<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<mapdb>
  <maps>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Sarengo Canyon</name>
        <description>
          The terrans that colonized the Koprulu sector originally traveled
          from Earth in four deep-space supercarriers. Three of those gargantuan
          ships delivered the colonists to their new homes relatively intact,
          but the fourth ship was not so lucky. The Sarengo crashed into the
          planet Umoja, killing all 8,000 of its passengers, and carving an
          immense canyon into the planet's surface. This canyon is now home to
          drifters, squatters, and other odd characters that hide amongst the
          broken rocks and scattered wreckage. The Umojan Protectorate has long
          proclaimed the entire canyon to be a restricted area, and this often
          leads to fierce conflicts when Protectorate security forces decide to
          sweep the area of intruders.
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(4)Sarengo Canyon Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(4)Sarengo Canyon.jpg</preview>
      <size x="128" y="192" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:1" />
      <features tileset="badlands" players="4" island="false" useMapSettings="true" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>1998-12-11</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Tropical Seas</name>
        <description>
          The Tropical Seas Resort has offered guests the ultimate in comfort
          and elegance for over three generations. Peaceful, sandy beaches and
          gentle palm groves are the natural setting for a stay filled with
          rest and relaxation. Although the resort has recently been enhanced
          by a Zerg infestation in the surrounding area, this is no reason to
          postpone your visit. The spirited fighting that occurs when well-trained
          Terran Marines dissuade the occasional Zerg incursion adds a new level
          of excitement to any vacation -- and what a story you will have to tell
          your friends! Guests can even sign up for an exotic Zerg Adventure--
          package and partake of a real "hunt in the wild" experience with the
          assistance of a trained guide. The Tropical Seas Resort promises your
          upcoming vacation will be unforgettable.
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(8)Tropical Seas Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(8)Tropical Seas.jpg</preview>
      <size x="256" y="192" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:1" />
      <features tileset="jungle" players="8" island="true" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>1998-12-18</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Gemini Station</name>
        <description>
          [[Universal News Network]]
          [[DEC HQ, Moria]]

          New Station Design Available

          The Dominion Engineering Corps (a division of the Kel-Morian Combine)
          proudly announces the availability of a new, low cost station design.
          The Gemini Series, a revolutionary step in space platform architecture,
          is suitable for nearly any orbital application. By utilizing a patented
          symmetrical structural layout, Gemini Series platforms can be constructed
          for half the cost of traditional station designs in half the time!
          Organizations or independently financed groups in need of a spaceborne
          facility for use in either business or pleasure applications should
          contact their local DEC representative for a presentation of the Gemini today.

          [[End Sponsored Segment]]
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(2)Gemini Station Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(2)Gemini Station.jpg</preview>
      <size x="96" y="128" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:1" />
      <features tileset="space" players="2" island="false" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>1998-12-22</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Christmas Rush</name>
        <description>
          Hearken back with us to those fond memories from childhood when
          unwrapping presents was a manic and enjoyable time laden with
          excitement and suspense. Now, imagine placing that joy and
          enchantment smack dab in the middle of Blizzard's .scm of the week!
          The result -- Christmas Rush, where you compete to see who can open
          the most presents. The best part about THESE presents is that they're
          both fun and functional since you can use them to stop the other
          players from taking more of YOUR presents! To top it all off, keep a
          sharp lookout for jolly old St. Nick who just may be stopping by to
          see if you are being naughty or nice. Happy Holidays from
          Blizzard Entertainment!
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(4)Christmas Rush Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(4)Christmas Rush.jpg</preview>
      <size x="128" y="192" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:1" />
      <features tileset="space" players="4" island="false" useMapSettings="true" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>1998-12-31</release>
    </map>

    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Dark Masters</name>
        <description>
          From the depths of a dark asteroid that lies deep in uncharted space,
          they watch and wait. Known only as the Dark Masters, they view all
          other beings as mere pawns to be manipulated in their quest for
          galactic dominance. Should they succeed in their plan, all sentient
          life in the universe will be forced into eternal servitude. Who will
          survive this galactic epic? The story unfolds Monday nights on the
          Galactic Entertainment Network -- entertainment for the new GENeration!
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(6)Dark Masters Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(6)Dark Masters.jpg</preview>
      <size x="96" y="96" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:2" />
      <features tileset="twilight" players="6" island="false" useMapSettings="true" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>1999-01-08</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Eldrich Lake</name>
        <description>
          Before the Zerg swarm ravaged Aiur, pilgrimages to sacred places across
          the planet by members of the Templar caste were a common undertaking.
          Many of these pilgrims traveled to a secret lake high in the mountains
          that was thought to contain mystic properties. Some went seeking serenity,
          while others were seeking self-awareness and a greater understanding of the
          universe. We've captured the essence of that lake in Naiad's new line of
          bottled water, "Eldritch Spring". Pick up a bottle and feel the magic today!
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(2)Eldrich Lake Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(2)Eldrich Lake.jpg</preview>
      <size x="128" y="128" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:1" />
      <features tileset="jungle" players="2" island="false" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>1999-01-15</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Untamed Wilds</name>
        <description>
          Some battles are fought over strategically located space platforms to
          increase the military's tactical position. Others are matters of honor
          to be settled on ancient Protoss proving grounds. Most encounters,
          however, occur by mere chance in the wilderness of the galaxy. In these
          skirmishes, battlefield intelligence can be scarce and fate does not
          always provide each combatant with equally defensible terrain. In the
          wild you can quickly find yourself in a situation that requires you to
          adapt or be destroyed.
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(8)Untamed Wilds Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(8)Untamed Wilds.jpg</preview>
      <size x="256" y="256" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:1" />
      <features tileset="jungle" players="8" island="false" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>1999-01-22</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Glacier Bay</name>
        <description>
          "Each Dominion Defense Force recruit must pass a battery of tests that
          are designed to determine if they are truly worthy to serve with the
          finest fighting force in the galaxy. The most grueling of these trials
          is code named Glacier Bay. The recruits are informed that they will be
          stationed at an outpost overlooking Glacier Bay for routine training
          exercises. To their dismay, Dropships land them on a nearby island and
          the prospective soldiers are forced to live off the meager resources
          that their landing zone provides. This requires these prospective soldiers
          to work up enough intestinal fortitude -- or disdain for their situation --
          to swim across the freezing waters to the mainland. This point is pressed
          once simulated hostile forces are thrown into the exercise."

          -- General Edmund Duke
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(4)Glacier Bay Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(4)Glacier Bay.jpg</preview>
      <size x="192" y="192" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:1" />
      <features tileset="ice" players="4" island="true" useMapSettings="true" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>1999-01-29</release>
    </map>

    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Heart Attack</name>
        <description>
          V is for Vultures, whose voices are strained
          A is for Archives, where Templar are trained
          L is for Larva, the Zerg's working class
          E is for Extractor, it gets Vespene gas
          N is for Nexus, a key Protoss factor
          T is for Titan, the Explorer's reactor
          I is for Infested, like Terrans exploding
          N is for Nydus, a canal quite foreboding
          E is for Ensnare, so you can't get away
          and this Map is for You, on this Valentine's Day
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(7)Heart Attack Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(7)Heart Attack.jpg</preview>
      <size x="256" y="256" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:1" />
      <features tileset="ice" players="7" island="true" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>1999-02-12</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Obsidian</name>
        <description>
          "The surface of Char can reach such extreme temperatures that mineral
          deposits become molten and form rivers of crystal that flow across the
          planet's surface. A recent application of space geodetic techniques to
          this phenomenon has measured the amount and spatial pattern of net
          vertical crustal deformation and shows that these rivers sometimes
          snake across the planetary mantle in this liquid state for months before
          finally hardening. Mineral laden pathways are then created and can be
          seen protruding from the obsidian landscape, serving as both landmarks
          and rich mining fields."

          -- Kel-Morian Combine GPS Survey Report
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(7)Heart Attack Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(7)Heart Attack.jpg</preview>
      <size x="192" y="128" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:1" />
      <features tileset="ash" players="4" island="false" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>1999-02-19</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Meat Grinder</name>
        <description>
          "You can't make me go back there."
          Sgt. Matthew Murdoch - Veteran of 2 tours of duty on Urthos III

          The small, mineral rich moon of Urthos III was one of the mostly
          fiercely contested territories during the recent UED conflict. It
          changed hands so often (and in such a bloody fashion) that the area
          eventually became known simply as the Meatgrinder. Thousands died
          there in pitched battles that often involved multiple forces from
          each species. Although the battlefields there are now quiet, ambitious
          leaders in search of crystals to fuel their ravenous machines of war
          tend to forget the costs of holding such a place...
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(7)Heart Attack Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(7)Heart Attack.jpg</preview>
      <size x="96" y="96" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:1" />
      <features tileset="jungle" players="8" island="false" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>1999-02-26</release>
    </map>

    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Shoreline</name>
        <description>
          The expansive shoreline of Heimdall IV is a peaceful setting where the
          bitter memories of battle can be washed away by waves, gently breaking
          over hundreds of miles of pristine beaches. The natural beauty of this
          planet has helped make it one of the more fashionable spots in the
          sector as the smell of the salt air and the bracing spray of the sea
          can restore the spirits of even the most shell-shocked veteran. The
          popularity of the sleepy resort setting has caused some unexpected
          occurrences, however, as members of opposing military forces sometimes
          decide to vacation there at the same time. It is only a matter of time
          before someone inevitably kicks sand in someone else's face and then
          the beaches become an impromptu battleground. Regardless of the outcome,
          the tropical rains always seem to wash away any signs of strife in time
          to prepare the beaches for the next gathering of those seeking rest and
          relaxation.
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(4)Shoreline Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(4)Shoreline.jpg</preview>
      <size x="192" y="192" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:1" />
      <features tileset="badlands" players="4" island="false" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>1999-03-12</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Scorpion Ravine</name>
        <description>
          The original strain of Scantid grew to a length no greater than 15
          Centimeters and was a common inhabitant of the desert regions of
          Korhal. The insect's mild venom, used to repel predatory animals,
          caused nothing more than mild rash and bothersome itching to those
          inadvertently stung by the shy animals. After Korhal was ravaged by
          nuclear fire in the surprise attack by the Confederates, nothing was
          left alive on the surface of the planet. Although the lowly Scantid
          survived in their deep underground communal burrows, exposure to
          massive radiation forever changed the creatures. Where once they had
          been nothing more than a footnote in Entomology journals, the Scantid
          were now monstrous beasts with claws capable of ripping a man in half
          and a stinger filled with an extremely lethal poison. If it were not
          for their lack of innate aggressiveness and the instinctive reflex to
          flee when threatened or injured, the Scantid may have over-run the
          planet, rendering Korhal virtually uninhabitable. Their communal
          instinct has also survived, and the area known as Scorpion Ravine is
          home to a large nest of the creatures. Although it seems dangerous,
          remember that the Scantid is more afraid of you than you are of it
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(8)Scorpion Ravine Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(8)Scorpion Ravine.jpg</preview>
      <size x="192" y="128" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:2" />
      <features tileset="desert" players="8" island="false" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>1999-03-19</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Mercenaries</name>
        <description>
          [[Universal News Network]]
          [[Outpost 782XJG, Koprulu sector]]

          The pirates of New Trinidad have been plundering the shipping lanes
          and outlying outposts across the Koprulu sector for decades. The
          constant governmental shifts, coupled with the recent UED conflict in
          that sector, have made the creation of a standing militia strong
          enough to deal with the threat impossible.

          In an attack launched from their impregnable space station over the
          empty world of New Trinidad, sustained shelling from Arclite Siege
          Tanks led to the death of Jacqueline Angel, heiress to the Angel
          Shipping empire. Reliable sources within the shipping conglomerate
          have reported the transfer of considerable funds to the accounts of
          local authorities for the expressed purpose of retaining groups of
          mercenaries to remove the pirate threat once and for all.

          [[End News Brief]]
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(3)Mercenaries Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <size x="192" y="128" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:1" />
      <features tileset="space" players="3" island="false" useMapSettings="true" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>1999-03-26</release>
    </map>

    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Egg Madness</name>
        <description>
          [[Universal News Network]]
          [[Universe Tonight, Special Report]]

          The ceremonies surrounding the celebration of many holidays have
          changed in both their meaning and nature over the centuries and the
          study and interpretation of these rituals has been the key focus of
          a consortium of Terran anthropologists here at the Kel-Morian
          Research Facility. Although scientists disagree on what the true
          meaning of the upcoming holiday known as Easter may have been, new
          findings may give us some idea on how this important event was
          observed by our ancient ancestors on Earth.

          Recent breakthroughs in data reconstruction have retrieved vital
          information from the salvaged computer wreckage recovered from the
          ancient Sarengo crash site. These restored files seems to confirm the
          current practice of celebrating Easter with gifts of small yellow and
          pink SynthEggs, cunningly crafted into realistic bird and bunny shapes.
          The custom of these gifts being delivered by a mysterious giant
          anthropomorphic Badger that wanders from sealed dome to sealed dome
          also seems rooted in fact, although the culmination of the day's
          celebration being a giant chrysalis hunt coupled with the wholesale
          slaughter of warring factions may be a more recent addition to these
          historic festivities.

          Wishing you and yours a Happy Easter This is Genna Xann, Universe Tonight

          [[End Transcript]]
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(3)Egg Madness Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(3)Egg Madness.jpg</preview>
      <size x="96" y="96" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:1" />
      <features tileset="installation" players="6" island="false" useMapSettings="true" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>1999-04-02</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Mirage</name>
        <description>
          My Brethren,

          Since the time of Khas, the visions have remained the same.

          A dark land of ancient plateaus and oceans of night... Night becomes
          day, and our ancient fathers aid us... We erase that which blights
          our face, but not that which lies within... The land that rests in
          twilight will be the place of our greatest triumph and also our
          greatest shame.

          Much to my dismay, many ages have passed since the prophecies of the
          "Place of Visions" have been paid heed. These visions resonate a truth
          beyond any simplistic comprehension, and I fear that they may foretell
          grave problems that lie just ahead. As keepers of the Khala, it is our
          duty to gather our most learned scholars to seek an understanding of
          these warnings as they may be the key to solving this crisis as yet
          unseen.

          - Excerpt from "The Letters of Tenarsis"
          (Dated 3 years before the destruction of Chau Sara)
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(6)Mirage Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(6)Mirage.jpg</preview>
      <size x="256" y="256" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:2" />
      <features tileset="twilight" players="7" island="false" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>1999-04-23</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Revolution</name>
        <description>
          In the dawning moments of the colonization of Sutur V two separate
          factions disagreed on how the lush green world should be developed.
          One side believed that a huge sprawling space station should be
          erected to further interstellar trade, and they could use giant
          robotic machines to extract the mineral wealth from the planet
          necessary for the station’s construction. These people managed to
          build the "Platform" over much of the Northern Hemisphere of the
          world. The builders and inhabitants of the Platform became known
          as the Northern Platformers or just the Northerners. Another faction
          held the life of the planet sacred, and committed to a plan of
          becoming one with the Planet and all its myriad life forms. These
          people were known as the Southern Druids, which was eventually
          shortened to the Southerners. These two opposing sides have been
          fighting in both the jungles to the south and the space platforms
          to the north for generations, so long that most of the people
          fighting and dying no longer know why. These unwilling warriors no
          longer wish to fight, but the leaders of both sides demand victory at
          all costs. The wildlife has mostly died out years ago, and the
          robotic mining machines have ceased to function, but still the war
          goes on.
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(6)Revolution Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(6)Revolution.jpg</preview>
      <size x="128" y="192" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:1" />
      <features tileset="space" players="6" island="false" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>1999-04-30</release>
    </map>

    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Bunker Command II</name>
        <description>
          "In this powerful remake of a true action classic, Bunker Command II
          recreates all of the excitement of the original strategic conflict
          while including all-new units to command. Lead your squad of
          experienced marines across a new and dangerous landscape, seeking out
          enemy bunkers to destroy before they can do the same thing to you. As
          you eliminate your foes and the bunkers they defend, reinforcements
          arrive to help carry on the fight for ultimate victory.
          Bunker Command II will prove to be the leader in the next generation
          of Real Time Bunker games."

          -Rexx Perry, V.P. of Bunker Command Marketing, UED Region
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(6)Bunker Command II Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <size x="96" y="96" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:2" />
      <features tileset="desert" players="8" island="false" useMapSettings="true" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>1999-05-07</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Ice Age</name>
        <description>
          After the larger of the twin suns supporting the lush pleasure world
          of Zenn failed, the paradise fell into an age of ice and darkness.
          Zenn remained in obscurity for decades, serving only as a stopping
          point and safe haven for smugglers and fringe world miners. This all
          changed when the frozen planet was named as the site for the New
          Dominion Winter Olympics, the premiere sporting event in Terran space.
          All went well until the ill-fated Plasma Rail Bobsled event...

          Although Olympic Security was prepared for possible trouble since
          Plasma Rail Bobsled fans are renowned as a rowdy and potentially
          violent bunch, no one could have anticipated the riot that erupted
          when the team from Korhal upset the favored Braxis crew in the finals.
          Screams of derision and empty beer canisters hurled in anger rapidly
          turned into gauss-rifle fire. Clashes in the streets of Zenn broke
          out between stolen Goliath security combat vehicles. The aggression
          spread like wildfire across the planet, soon becoming a struggle for
          survival on this inhospitable world. "The Riot" continues to this day,
          and though neither the Korhal "HeatBlisters" nor the Braxis "Glaciers"
          have emerged triumphant, their enthusiasm for the sport of Bobsledding
          remains undiminished.
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(6)Ice Age Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(6)Ice Age.jpg</preview>
      <size x="256" y="256" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:2" />
      <features tileset="ice" players="8" island="false" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>1999-05-12</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Up The Creek</name>
        <description>
          Terran Wildlife Services, in conjunction with LarsCorp Technologies,
          is proud to announce the grand opening of another soon to be wildly
          successful hunting preserve: The Creek. Designed as a small, intimate,
          and quiet locale with some of the finest combat fishing in the galaxy,
          the park caters to the tastes of the discriminating sportsman. "This
          new preserve should serve as a welcome haven for those seeking to
          avoid the crowds created by the overwhelming success of the better
          known ‘Hunters’ preserves," noted John Andrews, host of the popular
          "Better Living through Maximum Firepower" sporting show on the
          Galactic Entertainment Network.
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(2)Up The Creek Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(2)Up The Creek.jpg</preview>
      <size x="96" y="64" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:1" />
      <features tileset="badlands" players="2" island="false" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>1999-05-19</release>
    </map>

    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Black Hole</name>
        <description>
          The Summeria V station -- heralded as our final, finest hope for
          peace -- was fraught with problems from the day it opened. From Elder
          races struggling for political dominance to the drama and personal
          feuds among the members of the command staff, each week brought new
          challenges. Finally, the hand of destiny played the unkindest card of
          all as a small black hole tore through the very center of the vast
          complex. While some speculate that this fissure was created when a
          concealed Xel’Naga artifact went awry, others claim that the black
          hole had been there all along and was merely shifted into our time
          continuum during unauthorized weapon testing. In any case, the station
          inhabitants are left to battle both the gravity well of the black hole
          and the hostile aliens that are stranded at Summeria V until the
          massive station finally collapses under its own weight.
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(8)Black Hole Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(8)Black Hole.jpg</preview>
      <size x="256" y="256" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:1" />
      <features tileset="space" players="8" island="false" useMapSettings="true" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>1999-06-04</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Byway</name>
        <description>
          Byway originally appeared as the multi-player map "Byways" in the
          Shareware version of StarCraft. It is now being released as a bonus
          map of the week to allow players to play this map with the full
          version of StarCraft.
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(8)Black Hole Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(8)Black Hole.jpg</preview>
      <size x="96" y="96" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:1" />
      <features tileset="badlands" players="2" island="false" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>1999-06-11</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Slowburn</name>
        <description>
          The Interstellar Escape travel agency prides themselves on taking their
          clients to the most luxurious and pleasant surroundings that the galaxy
          has to offer. Pleasant sandy beaches and island casinos are the
          destination for many of these relaxation-seeking tourists. If you are
          looking for something a little bit more exciting for your upcoming
          vacation, check out Shipley Enterprises "Extreme Bodily Injury" set
          of destinations.

          "Slow Burn is our most popular adventure package, taking you to the
          blisteringly hot planet of Char, once home to the dreaded Overmind.
          You are shoved out of the dropship with a Kel-Morian multi-functional
          knife, a compass and three days worth of food. At this point you have
          one week to cover 350 kilometers of lava strewn Zerg infested rock
          and reach the pick up site. While this may sound trivial, the
          fluctuating magnetic fields that cover the surface of Char make the
          compass unreliable at best, and the cloud of ash that surrounds the
          planet seldom allows the stars to peek through to the surface. If you
          want a vacation that will leave your family with something to talk
          about for years to come, then try the Slow Burn."

          - "One Eye" McAlester, Sales rep for Shipley Enterprises
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(3)Slowburn Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(3)Slowburn.jpg</preview>
      <size x="128" y="128" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:1" />
      <features tileset="ash" players="3" island="false" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>1999-06-11</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Broken Mesa</name>
        <description>
          Broken Mesa was the site of a Dominion bio-weapons testing facility
          on the desert world of Korhal. Shortly before the UED assault on
          Korhal, Terran scientists created a new and potentially devastating
          plasma-pulse weapon. As reports of an approaching enemy fleet reached
          the high command on Korhal, testing was ordered in hopes that the
          power of this weapon might destroy the UED armada. While in the final
          testing phase, Senior Scientist Ozmel Dodds turned traitor as he
          attempted to curry favor with the attacking UED forces. On the day of
          the final test, Dodds changed the pulse-modulation frequency on the
          weapon causing the awesome cannon to overload, destroying itself and
          the research facility that housed it. What happened to the scientist
          remains a mystery to this day, but the Broken Mesa site still sees
          occasional conflict as various factions attempt to discover the
          remains of the weapons lab and the fabled plasma-pulse weapon.
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(5)Broken Mesa Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(5)Broken Mesa.jpg</preview>
      <size x="128" y="128" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:2" />
      <features tileset="desert" players="5" island="true" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>1999-06-18</release>
    </map>

    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Blizzard</name>
        <description>
          "It has come to the attention of this committee that one of our
          esteemed colleagues, Dr. Fredrica Wallis, has proposed a peculiar new
          theory that could shake the foundations of our very universe. A
          University sponsored geologic survey team returned six months ago
          from the icy wastes of Braxis, where they reported the discovery of a
          carving of immense proportions. Obviously created by sentient beings,
          this formation that bears some physical similarity to the word
          'Blizzard' was found in a section of snow measuring approximately two
          miles wide. Dr. Wallis has seized this report and is holding it up as
          evidence of her insane theory that our universe is merely a game
          simulation being played upon the personal computer of a higher life
          form. This committee refuses to grant this lunacy even the slightest
          shred of support. If Ms. Wallis wishes to continue with this research,
          we must recommend her transfer from the Physical Sciences branch of
          this University to the Metaphysics laboratory. At least in that
          setting she can ignore reality and continue to spout irrational
          nonsense to her heart's content. In short, she must not be allowed to
          infect other students or faculty members with these heretical ideas.
          We are all real flesh and blood, ladies and gentlemen -- we are not
          just a simulation."

          Partial transcript of Bian Ari's report
          Physical Sciences Steering Committee
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(6)Blizzard Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(6)Blizzard.jpg</preview>
      <size x="256" y="256" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:2" />
      <features tileset="ice" players="6" teams="2" island="false" useMapSettings="true" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>1999-07-02</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Mobius</name>
        <description>
          The existence of Protoss warp gate technology has conclusively
          demonstrated that instantaneous travel between the stars is indeed
          possible via artificial means. This raises the question, "might it
          then also be possible that such travel could transpire through a
          naturally occurring phenomenon?" While we have scant evidence to
          suggest that transdimentional rifts in space spontaneously exist,
          our understanding of the true nature of space and time is still quite
          limited. Now, let me show you something interesting. I can take this
          strip of paper, twist it 180 degrees as such, and then use a small
          amount of adhesive on the ends to form a loop. Suddenly, I have
          created a two dimensional object with only one side, commonly referred
          to as a Mobius Strip. You can trace your finger along the loop forever.
          A strange little creation, isn't it? What we see in this is a seemingly
          impossible construct of nature, yet I created it with a simple piece of
          paper and a bit of glue. Who of us really knows what strange enigmas
          remain to be unraveled in the vastness of the universe?"

          -Dr. Bazio Thurgood, Astrophysics Professor and host of the
          "Space is a weird, wacky place!" science show on the
          Galactic Entertainment Network.
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(6)Mobius Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(6)Mobius.jpg</preview>
      <size x="256" y="64" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:1" />
      <features tileset="badlands" players="6" island="false" useMapSettings="true" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>1999-07-08</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Pinwheel</name>
        <description>
          All across Shakuras lie strange places of power, many of which have
          not been fully probed by the nomadic Dark Templar who have made the
          twilight world their adopted home. One of these places is a foreboding
          and mysterious temple resting in the cracked earth of the remote Isle
          of Razjan. The four small shrines that lie in the temple connect to
          each other with almost perfectly symmetrical spiral paths sunken into
          the ground, forming what could only be a symbol of some cosmic
          significance. This peculiar complex may once have been a quiet,
          peaceful place for contemplation of the universe and the infinite
          beyond, but now the temple sees no such peace. The island temple lies
          well outside any established Protoss settlement or defensive outpost
          and this encourages raids on the complex by offworlders lusting for
          wealth, knowledge, and power.
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(6)Pinwheel Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(6)Pinwheel.jpg</preview>
      <size x="128" y="128" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:2" />
      <features tileset="twilight" players="4" island="false" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>1999-07-16</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Multiplication</name>
        <description>
          UED Military Academy Commandant's Log

          (Commandant Miloshek) "Gentlemen, we need to give our cadets a new
          challenge in the training simulators this week. Suggestions?"

          (Major Kilbourne) "Well, sir, it has been several weeks since we have
          had any deep space combat simulations. The last few exercises have
          mostly been recreations of ground battles."

          (CM) "An excellent idea, but I'd like to throw a twist into this sim."

          (MK) "Did you have anything specific in mind, sir?"

          (CM) "Hmm... give our Cadets an extreme amount of resources to start
          the campaign with so they won't feel the need to expand, but then
          create the additional resource nodes with even more Minerals and
          Vespene gas. Those that choose to expand should gain a huge advantage
          over those who simply stay put. I want battlefield commanders that
          are always on the move, gentlemen -- ones that are always looking for
          an edge in combat."

          (MK) "Very well, sir. We'll have the scenario programmed for this
          afternoon's exercise."
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(8)Multiplication Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(8)Multiplication.jpg</preview>
      <size x="192" y="192" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:1" />
      <features tileset="space" players="8" island="true" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>1999-07-23</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Abattoir</name>
        <description>
          I thought I had seen close combat.
          I thought I had seen the face of death.
          I thought I would live forever...
          Then they dropped us into the Abattoir.

          - Diary of Terran Marine 219XMS87632
          - Final Entry [End of Line]
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(8)Abattoir Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(8)Abattoir.jpg</preview>
      <size x="64" y="64" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:2" />
      <features tileset="twilight" players="8" island="false" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>1999-07-30</release>
    </map>

    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Cutthroat</name>
        <description>
          "In all my years of duty as a merchant captain in the space cargo
          lanes, the one thing I can be sure of is that there's pirates out
          there who will do just about anything to get your cargo. You can
          also be sure that the customs agents of the Kel-Morian Combine have
          hearts colder than the void of space, but that's entirely another
          story. The pirates, though, are always a problem for every honest
          trader trying to make a buck. Just when you think you've got your
          cargo home -- BAM -- those bastards come out of the woodwork to ruin
          your day and your pocketbook. One of these days they'll all get
          what's coming to them."

          -Captain Roberto Lamas
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(6)Cutthroat Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(6)Cutthroat.jpg</preview>
      <size x="192" y="128" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:1" />
      <features tileset="jungle" players="6" island="false" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>1999-07-30</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Firestorm</name>
        <description>
          When the surface of Korhal was scorched by the nuclear fire unleashed
          by a salvo of one thousand Apocalype-class missiles, the planet was
          not the only thing to be permanently scarred. The few survivors of
          the holocaust saw their families and homes turn to ash in a single,
          brief, blinding moment. The memory of that horror has hardened the
          remaining men and women of Korhal into some of the fiercest warriors
          in the Terran sector. With a complete willingness to use their own
          nuclear arsenal against any potential enemy, their nuclear firestorms
          have incinerated many unwary foes.
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(6)Firestorm Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(6)Firestorm.jpg</preview>
      <size x="192" y="128" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:2" />
      <features tileset="desert" players="6" island="false" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>1999-08-13</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Twisted Trail</name>
        <description>
          "Our detractors have accused us of catering to only hunters and
          combat fishermen with our wildly successful animal parks. Well, I am
          here to say to you good people that nothing is farther from the truth.
          Terran Wildlife Services actually has a wide array of parks that are
          not designed for the pursuit of sport at all. This dedication to the
          casual naturalist is exemplified in our Twisted Trail Park and
          Recreation Center. There is no finer hiking path in the sector, and
          this serene and peaceful area is normally far less crowded than our
          other reserves. I can't imagine a better spot for a calm, relaxing
          vacation away from the stress of civilization than in the fine
          outdoors. It's really a shame so few people ever get to see for
          themselves the exceptional beauty of this park."

          -Norman Goodfellow
          Senior Park Ranger, Terran Wildlife Services
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(2)Twisted Trail Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(2)Twisted Trail.jpg</preview>
      <size x="128" y="64" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:1" />
      <features tileset="badlands" players="2" island="false" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>1999-08-20</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Mountain Stronghold</name>
        <description>
          "The icy wastes of the planet Braxis provide a perfect environment to
          test both the physical and psychological fortitude of Dominion Defense
          Force recruits. Our soldiers must remain in fighting form in all
          possible battlefield conditions, and we have an impressive series of
          tests to weed out all the undesirables. My favorite training scenario
          is codenamed "Mountain Stronghold": a treacherous test of willpower
          and physical conditioning. The recruits must withstand an enemy
          onslaught for seven days with only three days worth of provisions.
          When the recruits begin to grow cold, and starvation sets in, we begin
          to bombard the fortress over a 72 hour stretch, culminating in a
          massive storming of their defenses by one of our crack assault teams.
          Those recruits who are able to overcome and survive this attack are
          rewarded with a new, tougher mission: Glacier Bay. Those who do not--
          are quickly disposed of."

          --Colonel Francis McCauly
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(4)Mountain Stronghold Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(4)Mountain Stronghold.jpg</preview>
      <size x="128" y="192" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:2" />
      <features tileset="ice" players="4" island="false" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>1999-08-27</release>
    </map>

    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Megalopolis</name>
        <description>
          "I have a dream, ladies and gentlemen. Mankind has been traveling
          amongst the heavens for generations, but our kind has never actually
          called space home. We've built orbital defense space platforms,
          'space stations' that provide waypoints for trade and commerce, and
          research facilities in space, but do we ever think of these places
          as home? No, we do not, and I aim to change that today. I've had the
          sector's finest engineers and designers build a place in the stars
          that humans can finally call home: Megalopolis. This new city will
          provide everything a family could need: great living quarters, great
          schools for all the kids, and great jobs for parents. We'll be opening
          up the city for new residents soon, so if you're interested in this
          wonderful opportunity contact us immediately! Space on the station
          is quite limited, and you don't want to be left out in the cold!"

          -Alan Johnson, Founder and CEO, Big Sky Inc.
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(8)Megalopolis Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(8)Megalopolis.jpg</preview>
      <size x="256" y="256" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:1" />
      <features tileset="space" players="8" island="false" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>1999-09-03</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Hellhole</name>
        <description>
          "Char? You want me to tell you about Char? Oh man, I still wake up
          screaming from the nightmares I have about that pit. A thick layer
          of ash covers everything, and there's this eerie red glow that comes
          from the magma that seeps up through the surface of the planet. One
          wrong step and you find yourself wading in a pool of hot lava. You
          ever hear the scream of a man as he is being burned alive by lava,
          Major? It's not something you soon forget, let me tell you. And if
          the infernal planet doesn't get you, there's always the damned Zerg
          that'll try and finish the job. Those devils were everywhere, and
          they killed a whole lot of my buddies in ways I don't want to
          remember. Char was a hellhole, alright, and I rather have you kill
          me than send me back there again."

          -Debriefing of UED Marine 384DTA47631
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(8)Hellhole Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(8)Hellhole.jpg</preview>
      <size x="256" y="256" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:1" />
      <features tileset="ash" players="2" island="false" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>1999-09-10</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Klondike</name>
        <description>
          The Koprulu sector has always been filled with prospectors searching
          the remote regions of planets for new, untapped mineral deposits. The
          Kel-Morian Combine tries to keep a tight lid on new discoveries to
          secure their exclusive mining rights, but news of virgin deposits
          sometimes leaks out. The resulting rush to secure the area by every
          mining company and private operator in the sector makes the fabled
          Klondike gold rush on Earth seem rather tame. The fight over a claim
          now usually sees the use of mercenaries, sabotage, and sometimes even
          nuclear weaponry...
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(6)Klondike Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(6)Klondike.jpg</preview>
      <size x="192" y="192" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:2" />
      <features tileset="ice" players="6" island="false" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>1999-09-17</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Watering Hole</name>
        <description>
          "Not every locale in the Koprulu sector is a hotbed of violence and
          mayhem. There are actually areas that are quiet, peaceful places to
          relax as the problems of the universe just pass you by. The secluded
          oasis known as the Watering Hole on the planet of Helioc III has a
          set of wonderfully scenic vistas where you can observe the beautiful
          native wildlife in their natural habitat. If you have the means, I
          suggest you give it a try as there's way too much stress in the
          galaxy these days."

          - Uran Golenko, leading stress therapist and featured guest on the
          popular "Universe Today" talk show

          TRAVEL NOTE: A sudden influx of tourists, coupled with the discovery
          of considerable mineral wealth on the planet, has left the ecology of
          Helioc III in a less than optimal state. Once the use of tactical
          nuclear weaponry has subsided, geologists expect a high level of
          planetary recovery.
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(6)Klondike Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(4)Watering Hole.jpg</preview>
      <size x="192" y="192" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:1" />
      <features tileset="jungle" players="4" island="false" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>1999-09-17</release>
    </map>

    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Zephyr Cove</name>
        <description>
          To the numerous artists who call it home, the colony of Tashai is a
          place of great inspiration. Nestled on a small island in a sheltered
          oceanic cove, the colony has idyllic weather throughout the year,
          and the scenic views of the sea never cease to amaze visitors. Ewan
          Welke, the greatest living bard of our time, has spent many years at
          the retreat composing poetry in an ancient form known as haiku. In
          fact, it was his now well-known verse that gave the colony its name,
          Zephyr Cove.

          peaceful island cove
          blessed by the ocean's cool breath
          the zephyr moves me
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(7)Zephyr Cove Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(7)Zephyr Cove.jpg</preview>
      <size x="192" y="256" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:1" />
      <features tileset="badlands" players="7" island="false" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>1999-10-01</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>New Venice</name>
        <description>
          Excerpt from the minutes of a recent meeting of the UED Naming Committee

            (Mr. Johnson) "Ok, ladies and gentlemen, we have been given the task
            of providing a name for the new orbital space station being built at
            Reynif II. We have been provided schematics of the station which I
            will put up on the holoprojector. Initial impressions?"

            (Mr. Smith) "It looks just like all the others - a big platform in
            space! I mean, come on, we keep getting these mundane assignments
            and it's getting harder and harder to come up with something memorable."

            (Mr. Johnson) "Be that as it may, Mr. Smith, we still have a job to
            do. Thoughts?"

            (Ms. Cole) "Well... It has a lot of bridges."

            (Mr. Smith) "Ha, So did ancient Venice -- but that doesn't help us much."

            (Mr. Johnson) "Excellent idea Ed! New Venice it is, then."

            (Mr. Smith) "What? Venice was a beautiful city of waterways, art,
            and romance. I don't see any of those things represented in the
            harsh architecture and brutish materials used to construct this
            station, Mr. Johnson. Why, we would be degrading and dishonoring a
            classic, nay a sacred icon of our Earth heritage!"

            (Mr. Johnson) "Well then, perhaps we'll have to work through the
            weekend on this one."

            *pause*

            (Mr. Smith) "I guess I can go with New Venice."
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(6)Zephyr Cove Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(6)Zephyr Cove.jpg</preview>
      <size x="192" y="192" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:1" />
      <features tileset="space" players="6" island="false" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>1999-10-08</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Turtle Island</name>
        <description>
          The universe is home to some rather odd geological formations that
          create a rich tapestry for astrologers, whether professional or
          amateur. On 20th Century Earth, for example, people could swear that
          there was a face on the surface of Mars. The location of the rocks
          and the eerie placement of shadows made envisioned mouth and eyes
          seem all too real. A prominent mountain range on the planet of
          Uilel IV looks just like a snake winding its way across the surface
          of the planet. One of the strangest of these planetary anomalies is
          found on an island just off of the main continent on Mar Sara.
          Explorers who first saw the island mistook it for a gargantuan
          turtle -- initially a cause for great alarm. Closer inspection
          quickly revealed the true nature of the landmass, but to this day
          nearby residents still call the place "Turtle Island."
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(6)Turtle Island Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(6)Turtle Island.jpg</preview>
      <size x="192" y="192" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:1" />
      <features tileset="jungle" players="4" island="false" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>1999-10-15</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Nukes Away</name>
        <description>
          "The most popular exercise in the Ghost training regimen is scenario
          A11-X93, commonly referred to by trainees as "Nukes Away". In this
          scenario, Ghosts practice a variety of covert infiltration techniques
          while gaining the technical knowledge necessary for the proper
          guidance of field-standard tactical nuclear weapons. Since nuclear
          weaponry is too expensive to be used in live fire training, the
          exercise is performed using an extremely lifelike holoprojection
          simulation. The competition between the teams of Ghosts can be extremely
          intense, and all too commonly we see recruits spending what little
          leisure time they have inside the simulation, honing their skills."

          -Commander Richard Walker
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(8)Nukes Away Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(8)Nukes Away.jpg</preview>
      <size x="192" y="192" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:2" />
      <features tileset="desert" players="8" island="false" useMapSettings="true" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>1999-10-22</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Ricochet</name>
        <description>
          In the chaos of the Zerg and UED invasions, their owners deemed many
          space platforms undefendable. These stations were hastily abandoned
          and standard operating procedure was to destroy the platform after
          the inhabitants were safely off to prevent the use of the structure
          by the enemy. A great many of these abandoned sites, however, escaped
          destruction. Gambling that the stations would be salvageable after
          the immediate crisis had ended, more than a few outposts were left
          intact as their owners figured that it was cheaper to refurbish the
          damaged platforms rather than completely rebuild. Pirates, bandits
          and smugglers looking for an out-of-the-way base for their criminal
          activities found these abandoned stations perfect for their needs.
          Perfect, that is, until the rightful owners came back...
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(5)Ricochet Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(5)Ricochet.jpg</preview>
      <size x="192" y="192" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:1" />
      <features tileset="space" players="5" island="false" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>1999-10-29</release>
    </map>

    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Indigo Waters</name>
        <description>
          "The destruction of our ancient home of Aiur still pains me. The
          blackening of our lands, the destruction of our cities and the
          defilement of our temples by the accursed Zerg leaves a void in my
          soul that can never again be filled. Now Shakuras is my new home,
          and I am finally beginning to understand why our exiled Dark Templar
          brethren settled here. I've spent many days just quietly gazing out
          at the strangely sad beauty of the water here. The waves hold the
          color of pure indigo and they mesmerize me and calm my soul. How
          could anyone leave this place after seeing such sights?"

          -Rassidan, High Templar of the Akiliae Tribe
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(6)Indigo Waters Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(6)Indigo Waters.jpg</preview>
      <size x="256" y="192" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:2" />
      <features tileset="twilight" players="6" island="false" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>1999-11-05</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Giant Steps</name>
        <description>
          "Who designed this [censored] place? What [censored] "engineer"
          crawled out from his [censored] hole to inflict this [censored]
          [censored] upon my people? A [censored] platform split into two
          [censored] halves?

          [CENSORED]!

          Why are there no [censored] bridges on this [censored] platform? Are
          we just supposed to [censored] leap off one [censored] half to the
          other? And to top it all off, those [censored] don't even provide
          enough Vespene [censored] gas for operations! [censored] this place!
          It's just one big [censored] [censored] [censored] [censored]!"

          -Edited comments of Colonel Riley "[censored]" Bullhorn
          Commander of Terran Orbital Platform G11-F3
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(2)Giant Steps Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(2)Giant Steps.jpg</preview>
      <size x="96" y="96" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:1" />
      <features tileset="space" players="2" island="false" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>1999-11-12</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Rock Garden</name>
        <description>
          Data Entry 1027AM0440:

          It looks like we've finally found a new place to call home. This
          planet where the Dark Templar have set up shop is very strange,
          though. I can get over the fact that everything here is blue -- in
          fact, it's actually kind of relaxing, sometimes. No, the true
          surrealism of this place is that I have never seen a single plant!
          No grass, no trees, not even a single bush to break up the landscape.
          All they do seem to have are lots and lots of rocks. It's damn odd...

          -Personal entry of Engineer's Mate Aaren Ruth, Renegade Battlecruiser Hyperion
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(5)Rock Garden Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(5)Rock Garden.jpg</preview>
      <size x="192" y="128" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:2" />
      <features tileset="twilight" players="5" island="false" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>1999-11-19</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Outbreak</name>
        <description>
          "What is it with the Koprulu Sector, anyhow? It seems like every week
          there's another skirmish, insurgency, sortie, planned offensive,
          counter strike, police action, border conflict or plain old-fashioned
          war breaking out. While the chaos and anarchy are great for a
          spacefaring merchant vessel that's willing to transport certain cargo
          of questionable legality, I sometimes have to stop and wonder if this
          madness will ever end. Of course, this is also right about the time
          the Captain slaps me upside the head and...

          "(external entry) Bailey, stop daydreaming and get back to work!"

          -Personal entry of First Mate Norris Bailey
          Recovery Vessel Starheaper
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(6)Outbreak Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(6)Outbreak.jpg</preview>
      <size x="256" y="256" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:1" />
      <features tileset="badlands" players="6" island="false" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>1999-11-24</release>
    </map>

    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Turnaround</name>
        <description>
          "Let your rapidity be that of the wind, your compactness that of the
          forest. In raiding and plundering be like fire, in immovability like
          a mountain. Let your plans be dark and impenetrable as night, and
          when you move, fall like a thunderbolt."

          Sun-Tzu, The Art of War
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(2)Turnaround Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(2)Turnaround.jpg</preview>
      <size x="128" y="96" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:2" />
      <features tileset="ice" players="2" island="false" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>1999-12-03</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Vulcan's Forge</name>
        <description>
          During the brief occupation of Char by the United Earth Directorate's
          Expeditionary Force, Admiral DuGalle instituted a series of intense
          training exercises on the forbidding surface of the planet. With the
          security of the now-tamed Overmind being the linchpin of further
          military success in the Koprulu sector, DuGalle needed to know that
          the harsh environment of Char would not make this task impossible.
          The horrifying firestorms and boiling pools of lava -- combined with
          the thick layer of ash that covered man and machine -- could cause
          serious physical and psychological strain on even hardened soldiers.
          Forces that were able to function on Char stayed and served as a
          garrison force. Those that couldn't "take the heat" were stationed
          elsewhere...
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(4)Vulcan's Forge Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(4)Vulcan's Forge.jpg</preview>
      <size x="128" y="128" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:1" />
      <features tileset="ash" players="4" island="false" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>1999-12-10</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Deep Freeze</name>
        <description>
          "Hell's supposed to be some kind of torture chamber filled with fire
          and brimstone, right? Well, after serving a tour of duty in the ice
          and snow of Braxis, the only difference I see is that at least Hell
          would be a lot warmer..."

          -Corporal Max Redius
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(4)Vulcan's Forge Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(4)Vulcan's Forge.jpg</preview>
      <size x="192" y="192" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:2" />
      <features tileset="ice" players="6" teams="3" island="true" useMapSettings="true" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>1999-12-17</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Twelve Days of Starcraft</name>
        <description>
          On the Twelfth Day Of Christmas, Blizzard gave to me...

          Twelve Arbiters
          Eleven Science Vessels
          Ten Ultralisks
          Nine Battlecruisers
          Eight Archons Burning
          Seven Zerglings Swarming
          Six Zealots Fighting
          Five Newborn Queens!
          Four Hydralisks
          Three Marines
          Two Terran Wraiths
          And a brand new SCV!
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(4)Twelve Days of Starcraft Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <size x="192" y="256" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:2" />
      <features tileset="ice" players="4" island="false" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>1999-12-23</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Mousetrap</name>
        <description>
          "The Bengalaas are not only one of the most colorful creatures in the
          universe, but are also counted amongst it's most feared predators.
          These jungle cats love to toy with their prey and have been observed
          slapping smaller creatures about in a sadistically playful manner for
          several minutes before finally making the kill with one swift bite to
          the neck. The predatory habits of the Bengalaas are not limited to
          small or defenseless animals, however. Exhibiting acutely intelligent
          hunting tactics, packs of Bengalaas can bring down an aggressive,
          dangerous target that is several times their own size. These noble
          cats are truly one of nature's finest and deadliest creations."

            - Benjamin Slater, Doctor of Zoology
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(4)Mousetrap Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(4)Mousetrap.jpg</preview>
      <size x="128" y="128" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:1" />
      <features tileset="jungle" players="3" island="false" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>1999-12-30</release>
    </map>

    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Crossfire</name>
        <description>
          "I used to think that defeating the Zerg would take precise military
          maneuvers, clever tactics and strong leadership. I was wrong. You
          can't out-think the swarm, you can't out-maneuver the swarm, and you
          certainly can't break the morale of the swarm. I hate to admit this,
          but I could do my job just as well if I ordered all my men to simply
          shoot anything that moves."

          -Colonel Ronald "Hardcore" Jackson
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(4)Crossfire Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(4)Crossfire.jpg</preview>
      <size x="192" y="96" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:2" />
      <features tileset="ice" players="4" teams="2" island="false" useMapSettings="true" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>2000-01-07</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Dead End</name>
        <description>
          "I reserve a particularly large chunk of bile in my stomach for the
          city of Graschek. My company and I were ordered to enter the town and
          destroy an enemy logistics base at that location. To make a long,
          intense, and particularly bloody story short, we lost our bearings en
          route and I lost half of my men. Admiral DuGalle himself probably
          would have become lost in that maze of streets and sewers. After my
          tour of duty is up, I'm going to find Graschek's city planners and
          kill them all with my bare hands..."

            -Lieutenant Thomas Dufay
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(4)Dead End Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(4)Dead End.jpg</preview>
      <size x="192" y="192" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:1" />
      <features tileset="badlands" players="4" island="false" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>2000-01-14</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Exile Station</name>
        <description>
          "To my dearest mother,

          I've been stationed out here at this deep space refueling depot now
          for three months, and the isolation here is maddening. Nearby
          astronomical phenomenon make normal communications difficult to the
          rest of the sector, and this only adds to our sense of being alone
          out here. Hopefully this message will get to you some time soon. I
          gave it to the captain of our monthly resupply vessel to forward to
          you. I love you, and miss you.

          Oscar

          P.S. I need new underwear, so if you send me some I'd really
          appreciate it. I know how you hate me wearing old, dirty underwear."
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(6)Exile Station Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(6)Exile Station.jpg</preview>
      <size x="192" y="192" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:1" />
      <features tileset="space" players="6" island="false" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>2000-01-21</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Execution</name>
        <description>
          "It’s been a long, arduous session for you cadets, and some of you
          must be getting really nervous that the final exam is almost upon you.
          You’ve heard plenty of pep talks from myself and the other trainers
          before this, so I will just say one last thing and then let you all
          start the simulation. Live as if your were to die tomorrow. Learn as
          if you were to live forever."

          - Training Coordinator Max Herai
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(2)Execution Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <size x="192" y="192" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:2" />
      <features tileset="twilight" players="2" island="false" useMapSettings="true" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>2000-01-28</release>
    </map>

    <map>
      <title>
        <name>New Aegean Sea</name>
        <description>
          MEMO 3451GS12
          FROM: Office of the Surveyor General
          RE: Naming Policies
          In the last few months I have seen a rash of new planets, continents,
          oceans, seas, lakes, rivers, mountains, plains and valleys with
          suggested nomenclature based on geographic features found on Earth.
          While I do not wish to single out any specific survey team as being
          particularly uncreative, it was brought to my attention that just
          today a body of water located on Exgelia IV was given the name
          "New Aegean Sea". I have examined the maps and photographs of the
          area in great detail and have read the survey report thoroughly.
          Although this body of water does indeed bear some resemblance to the
          Aegean Sea located off the coast of Greece and Turkey on Earth, it is
          with great hesitancy and reluctance that I give this name my final
          approval. Be advised that the next of these uninspired reports that
          comes across the desk of this office will be immediately rejected.

          WSM/es
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(8)New Aegean Sea Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(8)New Aegean Sea.jpg</preview>
      <size x="256" y="256" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:1" />
      <features tileset="jungle" players="8" island="true" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>2000-02-04</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Hailstorm</name>
        <description>
          "What’s that Command? A storm moving onto our position and we should
          seek shelter immediately? Sir, with all due respect, my men have been
          to the far reaches of the sector and fought off bandits, rebels,
          Protoss and even the Zerg. We are not afraid of some...
          [STATIC -- END OF LINE]."

          - Last transmission of Captain Jonathan Rogers,
          KIA during a freak hailstorm on Grnaki Prime
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(4)Hailstorm Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(4)Hailstorm.jpg</preview>
      <size x="192" y="128" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:2" />
      <features tileset="ice" players="4" island="true" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>2000-02-11</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Wide Horizons</name>
        <description>
          "I love a good desert. There's something about a huge expanse of
          seemingly barren wasteland that stirs something deeply in my soul.
          The blistering heat purges away all the outside cares of the world,
          leaving only the fragile core of my innermost being in its wake. The
          experience is just magical. Oh, and you can get a really awesome tan.
          Chicks dig a nice tan."

          - Gregory Raj, author and self-proclaimed "Guru of the Stars"
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(4)Wide Horizons Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(4)Wide Horizons.jpg</preview>
      <size x="256" y="192" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:2" />
      <features tileset="desert" players="6" island="false" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>2000-02-18</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Endurance</name>
        <description>
          "I don't understand how High Command can believe success is possible
          in this new "mission". We've fought back and triumphed against vastly
          superior odds before, but the prospect of facing SIX well- equipped
          strike teams worries even me. There's only so long a human can stay
          alert and fit in combat before finally succumbing to the need to rest.
          We're not robots here -- we're men and women made out of flesh and
          blood. If we are going to have any shot at coming out of this mess
          with our heads still attached we need to end the fight quickly. We
          can't let this fight turn into a war of attrition because if that
          happens, we won't have the resources or endurance to continue that
          kind of fight for long. Now you all know what's ahead of us, so let's
          go, go, go!"

            - General Tyco Eiche
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(2)Endurance Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(2)Endurance.jpg</preview>
      <size x="256" y="64" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:1" />
      <features tileset="jungle" players="2" island="false" useMapSettings="true" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>2000-02-25</release>
    </map>

    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Bull's Eye</name>
        <description>
          "Ok. I finally asked for a [censored] transfer. For once in their
          [censored] [censored] lives, High [censored] Command decides to do me
          a [censored] favor. So I move halfway across the [censored] sector to
          take command of my new station. What do I [censored] find?

          A [censored] [censored] more [censored] [censored] orbital platform
          then the last [censored] of [censored] that I was on!

          Some [censored] out there is just trying to [censored] with me, that
          HAS to be [censored] it. What [censored], [censored], [censored],
          [CENSORED] decided to build a [censored] Bull's Eye into the center
          of the [censored] platform? Can we make possibly things a little less
          [censored] easy for the [censored] enemy?

          [CENSORED]! "

          -Edited comments of Colonel Riley "[censored]" Bullhorn
          New Commander of Terran Orbital Platform K4-J19
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(4)Bull's Eye Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(4)Bull's Eye.jpg</preview>
      <size x="128" y="128" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:1" />
      <features tileset="space" players="4" island="false" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>2000-03-03</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Pyroclasm</name>
        <description>
          "I saw some horrible things on Char. Packs of Zerglings ripping
          entire platoons of Marines apart limb from limb. Broodlings bursting
          from the chests of my friends. Siege Tanks melting from a Guardian's
          acid spray. The worst thing I witnessed wasn't the Zerg, however, but
          how the planet itself decided to get involved in the killing. We were
          fighting near a large mountain when the top of it exploded. A cloud
          began rolling down the mountain, and it came at us FAST. I barely got
          out of its way, but over half of my platoon wasn't so lucky. This
          cloud just melted them all into twisted, sickening shapes that I will
          never be able to forget. The remainder of my assault team was pulled
          out of the conflict to regroup and in the debriefing afterwards, an
          intelligence officer explained what had happened. It seems that my
          unit was hit by a "pyroclastic flow". According to our scientific
          research, these "anomalies" can reach speeds of over 100 mph and
          temperatures higher than 800 degrees Celsius. The scientists can call
          it whatever they want -- I just know that I'll never forget what it
          did to my friends."

            -Diary of Corporal Aaron Parkinson
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(4)Pyroclasm Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(4)Pyroclasm.jpg</preview>
      <size x="128" y="128" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:1" />
      <features tileset="space" players="4" island="false" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>2000-03-10</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Backlash</name>
        <description>
          "There's been a lot of talk lately about the banning of wildlive
          preserves built for the sportsman in mind. Well, I've had enough of
          that talk. There's nothing more perfect in this world than looking
          down the barrel of a high powered gauss rifle built to penetrate 2
          inches of steel plating and seeing a defenseless animal square in the
          laser targeted, wind corrected, electronically enhanced scope with
          integrated night vision. NOTHING. Do these zealots understand the
          consequences of their actions? If we can't shoot a small animal, who
          knows what we might shoot next?"

          -Excerpt from an interview with Ralph Smith,
          Leader of the "Hunters are people, too!" organization
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(8)Backlash Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(8)Backlash.jpg</preview>
      <size x="128" y="192" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:1" />
      <features tileset="badlands" players="8" island="false" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>2000-03-17</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Whirlwind</name>
        <description>
          "The study of weather on alien planets, or Xenometerology, is one
          of the most exciting fields in Science today. Analyzing the wind and
          climate patterns of distant worlds will allow us to better predict
          the occurance of hazardous weather phenomenon that negatively impact
          our own homes and cities. Some of the weather events we've had the
          fortune to observe make the devastating whirlwinds back on Earth seem
          like a cool spring breeze. It is our responsibility to warn new
          colonists of the potential danger they may face before lives and
          property are utterly destroyed by the vengeful wrath of an alien
          Mother Nature."

          - Dr. Ula Isarki, Head of the Koprulu Meterological Institute
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(8)Whirlwind Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(8)Whirlwind.jpg</preview>
      <size x="128" y="96" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:1" />
      <features tileset="jungle" players="3" island="false" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>2000-03-24</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Desert Bloom</name>
        <description>
          "They cannot scare me with their empty spaces
          Between stars- on stars where no human race is.
          I have it in me so much nearer home
          To scare myself with my own desert places."

          - Robert Frost
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(5)Desert Bloom Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(5)Desert Bloom.jpg</preview>
      <size x="192" y="192" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:2" />
      <features tileset="desert" players="5" island="false" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>2000-03-31</release>
    </map>

    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Ursadon Flats</name>
        <description>
          "The barren, frozen wastelands of Braxis are some of the most
          unforgiving places in the sector. A thick layer of permafrost allows
          little in the way of plant life to thrive and brutal winter storms
          constantly rage across the plains. Even in such harsh conditions,
          however, the Ursadon thrives. This majestic beast is truly the lord
          of the tundra, having no natural enemies. Often found near ice floes,
          Ursadons are carnivorous creatures that hunt in the icy water for
          food. Instances of attacks on humans are thankfully rare, but the few
          recorded instances of an enraged Ursadon attack have always ended in
          tragedy. The Koprulu Wilderness Society recommends keeping a safe
          distance from these noble creatures while on Braxis, both for your
          own safety and that of the Ursadon."
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(5)Desert Bloom Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(5)Desert Bloom.jpg</preview>
      <size x="192" y="192" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:2" />
      <features tileset="ice" players="7" island="false" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>2000-04-07</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Mystique</name>
        <description>
          Data Entry 1102AM0441:

          A funny thing happened today. I watched a Protoss Templar doing what
          he calls "exercises." I was immediately taken back to the birthday
          party my mother gave me when I turned six years old. All my friends
          were there and there was more ice cream and cake than I could ever
          have thought possible. The highlight of the day, though, was the
          magician my mother hired as entertainment. He pulled a rabbit out of
          his black top hat and materialized coins out from behind the ears of
          my friends and, for a brief moment, I belived that magic was real.
          As an adult, I discovered the magic tricks that had transfixed me as
          a youth were just bits of misdirection and sleight of hand. I even
          learned a few of them to show my younger brothers and sisters. They
          loved those tricks, and I just wish they could see the Protoss. The
          Templar can do things with their minds that can only be described as
          real magic...

          -Personal entry of Engineer's Mate Aaren Ruth,
          Renegade Battlecruiser Hyperion
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(4)Mystique Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(4)Mystique.jpg</preview>
      <size x="192" y="128" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:2" />
      <features tileset="twilight" players="4" island="false" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>2000-04-14</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>High Noon</name>
        <description>
          "In ancient times dueling was an accepted and honorable means of
          resolving a dispute between individuals with opposing views. Two men
          would stand back to back on the field of combat -- their chosen
          weapons raised in a proud salute -- prepared to fight to the death.
          Things are a WHOLE lot different now. Lately, "Duels" are resolved
          with auto-aiming Gauss weaponry, powered combat suits, and even
          Goliath Combat Walkers! No one has respect for the old traditions
          anymore..."

            -Admiral David Jones
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(4)High Noon Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(4)High Noon.jpg</preview>
      <size x="192" y="128" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:1" />
      <features tileset="badlands" players="4" island="false" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>2000-04-21</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Hotspot</name>
        <description>
          "Locusts! That's what those infernal Kel-Morian Combine mining teams
          are! You think you have a good claim all to yourself, but then the
          Combine comes to ravage everything in sight right from under your
          nose. They'll leave me with nothing after they're done. Well I'm not
          going to take it anymore, and I've got just the thing for them! I'll
          make this a hot spot they'll never forget! I'll show them!"

            -Final Recorded Words of Usagi Hidalgo before the surface detonation
            of a 20 megaton nuclear device on the planet of Uilila IV
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(7)Hotspot Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(7)Hotspot.jpg</preview>
      <size x="192" y="192" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:2" />
      <features tileset="desert" players="7" island="false" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>2000-04-28</release>
    </map>

    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Face Off</name>
        <description>
          "Is there anything more tense and exciting in war then looking across
          the landscape to see your enemy on a hill knowing that he can just as
          easily see you? There's no where to hide. No complex manuevers or
          strategies are needed for victory. You butt heads like a pair of
          rams, determined to crush the enemy before they can do the same to
          you. It's an exhilirating feeling."

            -Officer's Journal of Colonel Abraham Vahn
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(2)Face Off Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(2)Face Off.jpg</preview>
      <size x="128" y="96" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:1" />
      <features tileset="ash" players="2" island="false" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>2000-05-05</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Frostbite</name>
        <description>
          The advent of the Powered Combat Suit for the common infantryman
          heralded a revolution in the making of war. For centuries soldiers
          have had to worry about rain, snow, wind, hostile atmospheres, and
          the cold hard vacuum of space. Any of these environments could make
          a soldier miserable and ineffective on the battlefield. Countless
          wars throughout history have been lost when the attacking army fell
          under the deep snowy blanket of a cold, cruel winter. How could men
          and women move with the strength sapped from their legs by the
          extreme cold? How could a weapon be fired if a trigger finger was
          numb from frostbite? The Powered Combat Suit has changed the face of
          modern warfare forever.
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(4)Frostbite Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(4)Frostbite.jpg</preview>
      <size x="128" y="128" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:2" />
      <features tileset="ice" players="4" island="true" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>2000-05-10</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Tropical Fever</name>
        <description>
          "Welcome to the jungle... it gets worse here everyday. You learn to
          live like an animal in the jungle where we play and if you’ve got a
          hunger for what you see, you'll take it -- eventually. You can have
          anything you want, but you better not take it from me..."

          -Speech given to new platoon members by Sergeant Axel "Guns" Enrozes
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(4)Tropical Fever Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(4)Tropical Fever.jpg</preview>
      <size x="128" y="192" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:1" />
      <features tileset="jungle" players="4" island="false" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>2000-05-19</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>The Void</name>
        <description>
          Status Report
          Station S630-M71
          Commanding Officer: Col. James Dather

          It has been two months since I assumed command of this station and
          I must regretfully report that the mythical reputation of the "Void",
          the colorful pseudonym for this place, is well deserved. The solar
          array mysteriously stops providing power once or twice each hour.
          Replacement parts for the environmental systems vanish into thin air.
          Quite simply, everything is breaking down. Of even greater concern is
          that one of the communication technicians died yesterday in the mess
          hall while eating rehydrated banana pudding. The station's medical
          officer is baffled, as the autopsy was inconclusive as to the cause
          of death.

          I have 4 months left in this current assignment and my only goal is
          to not see my advancement prospects vanish like everything else does
          in this God forsaken place.
        </description>
        <logo>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(6)The Void Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>broodwar-map-of-the-week/(6)The Void.jpg</preview>
      <size x="192" y="128" />
      <game gameId="sc:1" />
      <game versionId="sc:1" />
      <features tileset="space" players="6" island="false" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth:0" />
      <release>2000-05-26</release>
    </map>
  </maps>

  <authors>
    <author id="auth:0">
      <title>
        <name>Blizzard</name>
        <logo>authors/blizzard-logo.png</logo>
      </title>
      <url>www.blizzard.com</url>
      <email>contact@blizzard.com</email>
    </author>
    <author id="auth:1">
      <title>
        <name>John Doe</name>
      </title>
    </author>
  </authors>

  <games>
    <game id="sc">
      <title>
        <name>Starcraft</name>
        <logo>games/starcraft.png</logo>
      </title>
      <url>https://starcraft.com/</url>
      <versions>
        <version id="sc:0">
          <title>
            <name>Starcraft beta</name>
            <description>
              An online-only version of Starcraft open for public beta testing.
            </description>
          </title>
          <downloads>
            <full name="Beta">http://www.blizzardarchive.com:80/pub/Betas/SCBeta.rar</full>
            <full name="Japanese beta">http://www.blizzardarchive.com:80/pub/Betas/SCJBeta.rar</full>
          </downloads>
        </version>
        <version id="sc:1">
          <title>
            <name>Starcraft</name>
            <description>
              StarCraft is set around the early 26th century. Terran exiles from
              Earth have colonized a distant area of the Milky Way galaxy called
              the Koprulu Sector, having established several governments.
              Eventually, a civil war breaks out and ends with the formation of
              the Terran Dominion.

              However, humanity soon becomes caught in a war between the Protoss
              and the Zerg, which culminates at the end of StarCraft with the death
              of the Zerg leader, the Overmind, on the Protoss homeworld of Aiur.
              Without the Overmind to command, the Zerg rampage mindlessly across
              Aiur, while the cerebrates—the secondary commanders of the
              Swarm—attempt to regain control.
            </description>
            <logo>games/starcraft.png</logo>
          </title>
          <downloads>
            <demo name="Starcraft demo">http://ftp.blizzard.com/pub/starcraft/demos/SCDemo.exe</demo>
            <patch name="PC 1.16.1">http://ftp.blizzard.com/pub/starcraft/patches/PC/SC-1161.exe</patch>
            <patch name="MAC 1.16.1">http://ftp.blizzard.com/pub/starcraft/patches/Mac/StarCraft_v1161_OSX.zip</patch>
          </downloads>
          <release>1998-03-31</release>
        </version>
        <version id="sc:2">
          <title>
            <name>Starcraft: Broodwar</name>
            <description>
              After the discovery of alien life in the Koprulu Sector, the
              United Earth Directorate (UED) — the international body governing
              Earth — decides to send an expeditionary force to secure the
              sector and prevent the aliens from finding Earth.
            </description>
          </title>
          <downloads>
            <patch name="PC 1.16.1">http://ftp.blizzard.com/pub/broodwar/patches/PC/BW-1161.exe</patch>
            <patch name="MAC 1.16.1">http://ftp.blizzard.com/pub/broodwar/patches/Mac/Brood_War_v1161_OSX.zip</patch>
          </downloads>
          <release>1998-11-30</release>
        </version>
        <version id="sc:3">
          <title>
            <name>Starcraft: Remastered</name>
            <description>
              StarCraft®: Remastered upgrades the essential sci-fi strategy
              experience from beginning to end. Welcome back to the original
              game and its award-winning expansion, StarCraft: Brood War.

              We’ve remastered our units, buildings, and environments, improved
              game audio, and broadened our supported resolutions. Illustrated
              interludes bring the struggles and victories of heroes like Artanis,
              Fenix, Tassadar, Raynor and Kerrigan to life like never before.
              Most importantly, the strategy gameplay that StarCraft perfected
              years ago remains unchanged.
            </description>
            <logo>games/starcraft-remastered.png</logo>
          </title>
          <release>2017-07-30</release>
        </version>
      </versions>
    </game>
  </games>
</mapdb>
