<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<mapdb>
  <maps>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Brushfire</name>
        <description>
          The Protoss Templar have long used the ancient ruins of Mendella
          as a proving ground for promising disciples. The original settlement,
          built mostly underground, was flooded out during the Aeon of Strife
          when warring tribes destroyed a nearby reservoir in an attempt to
          drown their enemies. Recently, when the Zerg invaded Aiur, a nest
          from the Baelrog brood settled into the resource-rich area, and only
          a combined force of Protoss and Terran troops was able to cleanse the area.
        </description>
        <logo>starcraft-map-of-the-week/(4)Brushfire Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>starcraft-map-of-the-week/(4)Brushfire.jpg</preview>
      <size x="128" y="128" />
      <game gameId="sc-1" versionId="sc-1" />
      <features tileset="jungle" minPlayers="2" maxPlayers="4" island="false" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth-0" />
      <release>1998-05-22</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Divided Factions</name>
        <description>
          Even before Arcturus Mengsk and the Sons of Korhol overthrew the
          Terran Confederacy, several other rebellious factions fought for
          freedom. One such group, the Colonial Liberation Army, attempted
          to wrest control of the mining station Tyra by dividing the Confederate
          forces into smaller groups and fighting a series of skirmishes between
          opposing squads. In the end, the Confederate forces won the day with
          their "nuked earth" tactics.
        </description>
        <logo>starcraft-map-of-the-week/(6)Divided Factions Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>starcraft-map-of-the-week/(6)Divided Factions.jpg</preview>
      <size x="128" y="128" />
      <game gameId="sc-1" versionId="sc-1" />
      <features tileset="space" minPlayers="4" maxPlayers="6" teams="2" island="true" useMapSettings="true" />
      <author authorId="auth-0" />
      <release>1998-05-29</release>
    </map>

    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Eruption</name>
        <description>
          The Zerg chose Char as a launching point not only for its remote
          location and rich resources, but because the rough terrain provided
          many hiding places for various Brood hatcheries. While this undoubtedly
          helped the Zerg conceal their numbers from Terran and Protoss scouts,
          it worked against them when Kerrigan was forced to hunt down the Dark Templar.
          This map is typical of the twisting cliffs and magma pools of Char.
        </description>
        <logo>starcraft-map-of-the-week/(8)Eruption Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>starcraft-map-of-the-week/(8)Eruption.jpg</preview>
      <size x="128" y="128" />
      <game gameId="sc-1" versionId="sc-1" />
      <features tileset="ash" minPlayers="4" maxPlayers="8" teams="2" useMapSettings="true" />
      <author authorId="auth-0" />
      <release>1998-06-05</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Jacob's Ladder</name>
        <description>
          The Protoss Templar train constantly to maintain their fighting skills
          even during times of peace, rare as they are. Strategic wargames are
          carried out with a combination of real troops and hallucinations, and
          battlefields are chosen to allow the combatants an opportunity to hone
          a variety of tactical skills. This particular battlefield is a prime
          example and has been used for many inter-tribal competitions.
        </description>
        <logo>starcraft-map-of-the-week/(2)Jacobs Ladder Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>starcraft-map-of-the-week/(2)Jacobs Ladder.jpg</preview>
      <size x="96" y="96" />
      <game gameId="sc-1" versionId="sc-1" />
      <features tileset="jungle" minPlayers="2" maxPlayers="2" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth-0" />
      <release>1998-06-12</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Bunker Command</name>
        <description>
          The action is fast and furious as you lead your squad of soldiers
          on a search-and-destroy mission. You gain points for destroying
          enemy troops and bunkers, and points bring reinforcements, but beware--
          if you lose your bunker, your entire team is destroyed and you start over!
        </description>
        <logo>starcraft-map-of-the-week/(6)Bunker Command Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <size x="96" y="96" />
      <game gameId="sc-1" versionId="sc-1" />
      <features tileset="badlands" minPlayers="4" maxPlayers="6" useMapSettings="true" />
      <author authorId="auth-0" />
      <release>1998-06-19</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Elderlands</name>
        <description>
          One of the most sacred spots on Aiur is an ancient graveyard known
          as Ni Monn Adun, "Heart of Adun". Here the greatest of Adun's
          companions were laid to rest, and their psionic energy permeates
          the very air around the ancient site. Despite repeated attempts
          during their invasion, the Zerg were unable to occupy these grounds,
          for the Protoss fought with incredible ferocity to maintain the
          purity of Adun's Heart.
        </description>
        <logo>starcraft-map-of-the-week/(8)Elderlands Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>starcraft-map-of-the-week/(8)Elderlands.jpg</preview>
      <size x="192" y="192" />
      <game gameId="sc-1" versionId="sc-1" />
      <features tileset="jungle" minPlayers="4" maxPlayers="8" teams="4" island="false" useMapSettings="true" />
      <author authorId="auth-0" />
      <release>1998-06-26</release>
    </map>

    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Backwoods</name>
        <description>
          One reason the Terrans have been able to survive on the mostly-lifeless
          worlds along the rim for so long is that natural resources such as
          vespene gas and the mineral ores used in most construction slowly
          replenish over time, allowing mining companies to reuse decades-old
          excavation sites. One such site, Stickler Woods on Antiga Prime, became
          the focus of a series of skirmishes as Terran, Zerg, and Protoss forces
          alike moved in to take what they could.
        </description>
        <logo>starcraft-map-of-the-week/(8)Backwoods Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>starcraft-map-of-the-week/(8)Backwoods.jpg</preview>
      <size x="192" y="128" />
      <game gameId="sc-1" versionId="sc-1" />
      <features tileset="badlands" minPlayers="4" maxPlayers="8" teams="2" island="false" useMapSettings="true" />
      <author authorId="auth-0" />
      <release>1998-07-03</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Zerg Soccer</name>
        <description>
          Most people assume that the Zerg are a malicious species with no sense
          of humor or fun. While they are quite malicious, some Cerebrates have
          demonstrated both humor and a desire for pure recreation. The recent
          popularity of soccer among the Swarm is a prime example. Besides
          sporting a name even a Hydralisk can pronounce, it gives opposing
          Broods an opportunity to safely compete, and has recently surpassed
          "Pin your tail through the Terran" as the Zerg sport of choice.
        </description>
        <logo>starcraft-map-of-the-week/(2)Zerg Soccer Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <size x="192" y="128" />
      <game gameId="sc-1" versionId="sc-1" />
      <features tileset="jungle" minPlayers="2" maxPlayers="2" island="false" useMapSettings="true" />
      <author authorId="auth-0" />
      <release>1998-07-10</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Expedition</name>
        <description>
          The Zerg invasion of Aiur brought untold death and devastation to the
          planet, but in many ways the darkest days in the history of the Protoss
          were shortly before the departure of the Dark Templar, when the barely
          reunited tribes began to fight once more. Old vendettas and ancient
          prejudices were reborn as the Protoss who refused the way of Khala were
          branded as traitors and hunted down. Grand battles scarred the surface
          and many bold warriors were slain in massive engagements. This map allows
          you to recreate those epic campaigns, and see how the presence of Terran
          and Zerg forces might have mixed things up.
        </description>
        <logo>starcraft-map-of-the-week/(8)Expedition Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>starcraft-map-of-the-week/(8)Expedition.jpg</preview>
      <size x="256" y="256" />
      <game gameId="sc-1" versionId="sc-1" />
      <features tileset="jungle" minPlayers="4" maxPlayers="8" teams="2" island="false" useMapSettings="true" />
      <author authorId="auth-0" />
      <release>1998-07-17</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Nova Station</name>
        <description>
          Long known for their clandestine operations, the Confederate's
          enigmatic Nova Squadron was created not only to gather intelligence
          on the various "Pirate Militias" that threatened Confederate security,
          but also to keep tabs on the various operative branches within the
          Confederate Armed Forces. Once the Confederacy was dissolved, Nova Squadron
          was forced to go into hiding. Whoever can maintain control of their former
          headquarters not only commands the most strategically advantageous site
          in the whole sector, but also has access to whatever priceless intelligence
          Nova Squadron may have left behind.
        </description>
        <logo>starcraft-map-of-the-week/(4)Nova Station Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>starcraft-map-of-the-week/(4)Nova Station.jpg</preview>
      <size x="128" y="128" />
      <game gameId="sc-1" versionId="sc-1" />
      <features tileset="space" minPlayers="2" maxPlayers="4" teams="2" island="false" useMapSettings="true" />
      <author authorId="auth-0" />
      <release>1998-07-24</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Predators</name>
        <description>
          Long ago, the Asari hunting grounds were favored by the mighty Protoss
          who Stalked through their jungle-infested valleys. Now, as the world
          of Aiur has been invaded by marauding alien races, the Protoss rush to
          protect their once sacred lands. The hunters shall hunt again… And no
          creature shall leave Asari alive.
        </description>
        <logo>starcraft-map-of-the-week/(5)Predators Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>starcraft-map-of-the-week/(5)Predators.jpg</preview>
      <size x="128" y="128" />
      <game gameId="sc-1" versionId="sc-1" />
      <features tileset="space" minPlayers="2" maxPlayers="5" island="false" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth-0" />
      <release>1998-07-31</release>
    </map>

    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Warp Gates</name>
        <description>
          In the Aeon of Strife, Protoss warriors created warp gates to travel
          great distances instantaneously. The knowledge involved in their
          creation has been lost, but on some planets, these gates still remain.
          When these sites are discovered, they spawn some of the most violent
          battles as great powers try and control these ancient places of power.
          A series of these gates have been discovered and you and an Allied
          team have been dispatched to control these gates and discover the
          mysteries they contain.
        </description>
        <logo>starcraft-map-of-the-week/(4)Warp Gates Logo.jpg</logo>
      </title>
      <!-- TODO: preview -->
      <size x="128" y="128" />
      <game gameId="sc-1" versionId="sc-1" />
      <features tileset="jungle" minPlayers="2" maxPlayers="4" teams="2" island="false" useMapSettings="true" />
      <author authorId="auth-0" />
      <release>1998-08-07</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Ghost Town</name>
        <description>
          Chau Sara has been a flash point for unparalleled hostilities during
          the Wars. Seeding the atmosphere with toxic spores, the Zerg enslaved
          the Terran population that founded the colony and changed the surface
          of the world to better support their Hive clusters. Then, out of the
          cold endlessness of space, a great Protoss fleet arrived and, seeking
          to prevent further infestation, incinerated the planet. Since that time,
          Chau Sara has been a lifeless world hanging in the void.
        </description>
        <logo>starcraft-map-of-the-week/(6)Ghost Town Logo.jpg</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>starcraft-map-of-the-week/(6)Ghost Town.jpg</preview>
      <size x="192" y="128" />
      <game gameId="sc-1" versionId="sc-1" />
      <features tileset="badlands" minPlayers="2" maxPlayers="6" island="false" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth-0" />
      <release>1998-08-14</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Enigma</name>
        <description>
          Strange symbols based on ancient, sacred geometries that embodied a
          comprehensive knowledge of proportion and ratio have been a part of
          Terran culture since the late 17th century of their recorded history.
          It was later believed that these symbols were created when alien craft
          landed in fields -- a theory supported by the fact that aerial
          phenomenon had been observed in connection with the discovery of
          these formations.

          When these key shapes began appearing on desolate platforms at the edge
          of known space, the Terrans dispatched teams of scientists in an attempt
          to finally learn whether these were simple plasma induced phenomenon
          or intelligently controlled formations with universal teaching.
          The truth is out there...
        </description>
        <logo>starcraft-map-of-the-week/(8)Enigma Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>starcraft-map-of-the-week/(8)Enigma.jpg</preview>
      <size x="192" y="192" />
      <game gameId="sc-1" versionId="sc-1" />
      <features tileset="space" minPlayers="2" maxPlayers="8" teams="2" island="false" useMapSettings="true" />
      <author authorId="auth-0" />
      <release>1998-08-21</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Friends '98</name>
        <description>
          The constant strife and warfare that has divided our species has led
          us now to follow a new and shining path gilded with cooperation. With
          our new found allies, we shall begin to build an enlightened
          civilization of truth, honor and beauty. We will forge a new and
          lasting peace... a peace through superior firepower...
        </description>
        <logo>starcraft-map-of-the-week/(8)Friends98 Logo.jpg</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>starcraft-map-of-the-week/(8)Friends98.jpg</preview>
      <size x="192" y="192" />
      <game gameId="sc-1" versionId="sc-1" />
      <features tileset="jungle" minPlayers="4" maxPlayers="8" teams="2" island="false" useMapSettings="true" />
      <author authorId="auth-0" />
      <release>1998-08-21</release>
    </map>

    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Legacy</name>
        <description>
          Many religious sites were destroyed in the great war, and the ancient
          temples of Braken were of no exception. The invasive jungles of this
          verdant world have all but restored the planet to its natural state.
          It is still rich -- not only with the resources that fuel the great
          war machines of the stars -- but also in arcane religious significance.
          The prophesies foretell that "he who harnesses this world will someday
          wield great a power, sanctified by the ancient ones". Securing this
          essential part of the sector would bring great honor, glory and riches
          to the one who could hold it...
        </description>
        <logo>starcraft-map-of-the-week/(6)Legacy Logo.jpg</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>starcraft-map-of-the-week/(6)Legacy.jpg</preview>
      <size x="128" y="128" />
      <game gameId="sc-1" versionId="sc-1" />
      <features tileset="jungle" minPlayers="2" maxPlayers="6" teams="2" island="false" useMapSettings="true" />
      <author authorId="auth-0" />
      <release>1998-09-04</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Steal the Beacon</name>
        <description>
          Many religious sites were destroyed in the great war, and the ancient
          temples of Braken were of no exception. The invasive jungles of this
          verdant world have all but restored the planet to its natural state.
          It is still rich -- not only with the resources that fuel the great
          war machines of the stars -- but also in arcane religious significance.
          The prophesies foretell that "he who harnesses this world will someday
          wield great a power, sanctified by the ancient ones". Securing this
          essential part of the sector would bring great honor, glory and riches
          to the one who could hold it...
        </description>
        <logo>starcraft-map-of-the-week/(4)Steal the Beacon Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>starcraft-map-of-the-week/(4)Steal the Beacon.jpg</preview>
      <size x="96" y="96" />
      <game gameId="sc-1" versionId="sc-1" />
      <features tileset="installation" minPlayers="2" maxPlayers="4" island="false" useMapSettings="true" />
      <author authorId="auth-0" />
      <release>1998-09-04</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Chain Lightning</name>
        <description>
          The summer storms that ravage the high plateaus of Aiur appear and
          vanish in the blink of an eye. Fierce battles for control of the
          plateaus’ vast mineral fields are as swift as the storms that envelop
          them. The current devastation wrought upon Aiur has forced the
          combatants to this new proving ground, where the fighting has begun anew.
        </description>
        <logo>starcraft-map-of-the-week/(6)Chain Lightning Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>starcraft-map-of-the-week/(6)Chain Lightning.jpg</preview>
      <size x="128" y="96" />
      <game gameId="sc-1" versionId="sc-1" />
      <features tileset="jungle" minPlayers="2" maxPlayers="6" island="false" useMapSettings="true" />
      <author authorId="auth-0" />
      <release>1998-09-11</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Aurora</name>
        <description>
          Now and again a giant platform is seen drifting through space,
          accompanied by a strange set of lights following in an eerie glow.
          Rumored to be the remains of an experimental arboretum platform
          jettisoned during the destruction of Korhal, the platform is said
          to contain a secret lab dedicated to the creation of strange and
          exotics plants. Plants, whose purpose remains unknown to this day.
        </description>
        <logo>starcraft-map-of-the-week/(8)Aurora Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>starcraft-map-of-the-week/(8)Aurora.jpg</preview>
      <size x="256" y="192" />
      <game gameId="sc-1" versionId="sc-1" />
      <features tileset="space" minPlayers="2" maxPlayers="8" island="false" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth-0" />
      <release>1998-09-18</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Inferno</name>
        <description>
          When volcanic forces tear a planet apart, it twists the surface world
          into unrecognizable and bizarre shapes. The planet Wotan II was once
          a peaceful agrarian world until a confederate extremist detonated a
          Mercer class doomsday device deep within the planet's core. The
          explosion brought forth to the surface the natural riches of this world
          and now many factions struggle to survive the fiery surface long enough
          to harvest the treasures that this world has to offer.
        </description>
        <logo>starcraft-map-of-the-week/(4)Inferno Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>starcraft-map-of-the-week/(4)Inferno.jpg</preview>
      <size x="192" y="192" />
      <game gameId="sc-1" versionId="sc-1" />
      <features tileset="ash" minPlayers="2" maxPlayers="4" island="false" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth-0" />
      <release>1998-09-25</release>
    </map>

    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Labyrinth</name>
        <description>
          The Kel-Morian combine has been exploiting the ore deposits of remote
          worlds for decades. From time to time, their mining teams unearth
          strange artifacts or other physical evidence ancient civilizations.
          This was the case when they discovered a monstrous labyrinth at the
          Warrant VI dig site. Carbon dating shows that this gigantic series of
          underground caves dates back several millennia. Several Terran scholars
          have noted strong similarities between this maze and the patterns found
          in the Labyrinth of Crete, indicating that there may have been alien
          visitors on Earth long ago. This is, of course, secondary to the discovery
          of extensive mineral fields within the labyrinth to the Kel-Morian combine,
          and it seems unlikely that they would be interested in simply turning their
          find over to "the scientific community" without a fight.
        </description>
        <logo>starcraft-map-of-the-week/(8)Labyrinth Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>starcraft-map-of-the-week/(8)Labyrinth.jpg</preview>
      <size x="192" y="256" />
      <game gameId="sc-1" versionId="sc-1" />
      <features tileset="badlands" minPlayers="2" maxPlayers="8" island="false" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth-0" />
      <release>1998-10-02</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Big Game Hunters</name>
        <description>
          The Hunt continues with Big Game resources. Terran Wildlife Services,
          in conjunction with LarsCorp Technologies, has announced the grand
          opening of their fantastic new hunting preserve known as "Big Game".
          Spawned from the overwhelming success of their "Hunters" park, this
          new preserve was created to provide an environment that is safe,
          controlled, and extremely challenging.

          "Ballistic sporting has been so universally accepted that many citizens
          in the private sector have even created their own private hunting grounds,"
          said Todd Coyle, chairman of the Committee for the Recreational Use of
          Sidearms and High-explosives (CRUSH). "This new facility has even more
          of what sportsmen have asked for, and we know the true 'Big Game Hunters'
          will quickly join in the fun."
        </description>
        <logo>starcraft-map-of-the-week/(8)Big Game Hunters Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>starcraft-map-of-the-week/(8)Big Game Hunters.jpg</preview>
      <size x="128" y="128" />
      <game gameId="sc-1" versionId="sc-1" />
      <features tileset="jungle" minPlayers="2" maxPlayers="8" island="false" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth-0" />
      <release>1998-10-09</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Acropolis</name>
        <description>
          Recent explorations have uncovered a previously uncharted island on
          the jungle planet of Ynoth. Located at the center of this island are
          six massive citadels surrounding the ruins of a seventh. This has
          caused a stir amongst the Shelak tribe as the Protoss seer Khyar
          wrote several cryptic passages concerning an mystic Acropolis
          referred to "The Six and The One". While it written in his works that,
          "...the ruler of the Six shall use the One to become the Only..."
          Khyar was also called the Mad Prophet in more than one historical
          record. Whether this power is real or merely legend, there is a great
          deal of interest in controlling this island as well as the ancient
          citadels.
        </description>
        <logo>starcraft-map-of-the-week/(6)Acropolis Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>starcraft-map-of-the-week/(6)Acropolis.jpg</preview>
      <size x="192" y="192" />
      <game gameId="sc-1" versionId="sc-1" />
      <features tileset="jungle" minPlayers="2" maxPlayers="6" island="false" useMapSettings="false" ladder="true" />
      <author authorId="auth-0" />
      <release>1998-10-09</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Catwalk Alley</name>
        <description>
          [[Universal News Network]]
          [[Theta Prime Station, Tarsonis]]

          New Station Unveiled

          The Dominion Engineering Corps (a division of the Kel-Morian Combine)
          has taken up the task of rebuilding the many vital orbital platforms
          required for a healthy flow of commerce in the aftermath of recent
          upheaval and subsequent demise of the Terran Confederacy. The DEC is
          utilizing many new design elements in the construction of these stations,
          and the Theta Prime supply depot orbiting Tarsonis is a shining example
          of innovative thinking. Coined "Catwalk Alley" by the project engineers,
          the ingenious use of elevated catwalks provides a host of improved
          station functions, including easier maintenance and better defensibility
          from insurgent forces. The station is expected to serve as a showcase for
          the power and ingenuity of the Dominion for many centuries.

          [[End News Brief]]
        </description>
        <logo>starcraft-map-of-the-week/(4)Catwalk Alley Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>starcraft-map-of-the-week/(4)Catwalk Alley.jpg</preview>
      <size x="128" y="128" />
      <game gameId="sc-1" versionId="sc-1" />
      <features tileset="space" minPlayers="2" maxPlayers="4" island="false" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth-0" />
      <release>1998-10-09</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Polaris Prime</name>
        <description>
          Originally designed as a diplomatic enclave, Polaris Prime was envisioned
          as a place where disparate factions would gather and work out their
          differences in a peaceful manner. The station, consisting of two central
          meeting areas and six separated rooms, were well suited for the needs of
          visiting Ambassadors and their staff. The station gained a well-earned
          reputation as a haven for those individuals dedicated to peace. That all
          changed when the Zerg onslaught began. Polaris Prime was quickly abandoned
          when it fell into the ravenous path of the Swarm. Now, diplomacy of a
          different kind has begun, as those species that once spoke of peace return
          to present their arguments in a more aggressive manner.
        </description>
        <logo>starcraft-map-of-the-week/(6)Polaris Prime Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>starcraft-map-of-the-week/(6)Polaris Prime.jpg</preview>
      <size x="192" y="192" />
      <game gameId="sc-1" versionId="sc-1" />
      <features tileset="space" minPlayers="2" maxPlayers="6" island="true" useMapSettings="false" ladder="true" />
      <author authorId="auth-0" />
      <release>1998-10-16</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>The New Gauntlet</name>
        <description>
          After the Swarms settled the world where the old Gauntlet had been
          built and all attempts to dislodge them failed, Emperor Mengsk decreed
          that a new one be erected. This new Gauntlet was built in a sector of
          space much harder for the swarms to overrun. The engineers who built
          this new Gauntlet tried to use the original blueprints, but there is no
          doubt that some minor but nevertheless important differences crept into
          its construction.
        </description>
        <logo>starcraft-map-of-the-week/(2)New Gauntlet Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>starcraft-map-of-the-week/(2)New Gauntlet.jpg</preview>
      <size x="128" y="96" />
      <game gameId="sc-1" versionId="sc-1" />
      <features tileset="badlands" minPlayers="2" maxPlayers="2" island="false" useMapSettings="false" ladder="true" />
      <author authorId="auth-0" />
      <release>1998-10-23</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Proving Grounds</name>
        <description>
          The ancient, vicious blood feuds that were born in the Aeon of Strife
          virtually flooded the proving grounds on Gyras with the life force of
          thousands of Protoss Warriors. This bloodshed ended when the mystic
          Khas called upon the forces of the Khaydarin Crystals and destroyed
          the arena. The ruins that now stand here serve as a grim reminder of
          both what has passed, and the purpose that this place now serves.
          Although Khas strove to bring unification and enlightenment to his
          people, he also knew that some disputes would still demand resolution
          through force. Therefore, this place was sanctified as an arena of
          honor, and those who seek to settle personal matters come back to
          Gyras to prove their mettle in battle.
        </description>
        <logo>starcraft-map-of-the-week/(4)Proving Grounds Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>starcraft-map-of-the-week/(4)Proving Grounds.jpg</preview>
      <size x="128" y="128" />
      <game gameId="sc-1" versionId="sc-1" />
      <features tileset="jungle" minPlayers="2" maxPlayers="4" island="false" useMapSettings="false" ladder="true" />
      <author authorId="auth-0" />
      <release>1998-10-23</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Blast Furnace</name>
        <description>
          The temperatures on the planet Char can become so intense that large
          portions of the planet's surface become completely liquefied. During
          certain times, when the planet is furthest from the twin suns of the
          system, small islands form on top of these seas of magma. These bits
          of land are, not surprisingly, replete with minerals and greatly
          prized as sources of incredible wealth. These riches are not without
          cost, however, as more than one potential prospector has met his
          demise within the fierce heat of Char.
        </description>
        <logo>starcraft-map-of-the-week/(6)Blast Furnace Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>starcraft-map-of-the-week/(6)Blast Furnace.jpg</preview>
      <size x="192" y="192" />
      <game gameId="sc-1" versionId="sc-1" />
      <features tileset="ash" minPlayers="2" maxPlayers="6" island="false" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth-0" />
      <release>1998-10-30</release>
    </map>

    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Turbo</name>
        <description>
          Originally designed as a means to test and observe the reactions of
          prospective battlefield commanders under rapidly changing battlefield
          conditions, the Arclite Turbo Simulator 2000-- has evolved into a way
          of life for a section of the military elite. The ATS2000-- duplicates
          a standard combat environment and then increases the tempo of combat
          to such a degree that even the most competent officers have trouble
          keeping up with the ever-changing tide of events. Commanders who can
          master this simulation will almost certainly be able to dominate their
          enemies once placed in normal battlefield conditions.
        </description>
        <logo>starcraft-map-of-the-week/(8)Turbo Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>starcraft-map-of-the-week/(8)Turbo.jpg</preview>
      <size x="192" y="192" />
      <game gameId="sc-1" versionId="sc-1" />
      <features tileset="jungle" minPlayers="2" maxPlayers="8" island="false" useMapSettings="true" />
      <author authorId="auth-0" />
      <release>1998-11-06</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>The Highway</name>
        <description>
          The Terran frontier has remained a place devoid of any semblance of
          law and order for decades. On the desolate strips of prefabricated
          roadway that stretch between border colonies, gangs and outcast
          aliens terrorize any wayward travelers foolish enough to encroach
          into their territory. Traders and treasure seekers use these dangerous
          byways at their own risk. When two or more gangs square off in arguments
          over salvage rights or in border disputes, these highways host battles
          unrivaled in their ferocity and violence.
        </description>
        <logo>starcraft-map-of-the-week/(4)The Highway Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>starcraft-map-of-the-week/(4)The Highway.jpg</preview>
      <size x="192" y="128" />
      <game gameId="sc-1" versionId="sc-1" />
      <features tileset="badlands" minPlayers="2" maxPlayers="4" teams="2" island="false" useMapSettings="true" />
      <author authorId="auth-0" />
      <release>1998-11-06</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Garden of Aiur</name>
        <description>
          Since its creation at the end of the Aeon of Strife, a sacred garden
          has been a maintained as a center for peace, tranquility and reflection
          upon the ways of the Khala. Following the destruction of Aiur's
          defenders at the hands of the Zerg, the garden became a focal point for
          pitched conflicts between the ravenous Swarm, mercenary Terrans in search
          of salvage, and the few remaining Protoss forces. Whether you have come
          to destroy this place or protect it, the blood of your enemies will
          ensure that the garden remains well watered.
        </description>
        <logo>starcraft-map-of-the-week/(8)Garden Of Aiur Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>starcraft-map-of-the-week/(8)Garden Of Aiur.jpg</preview>
      <size x="192" y="192" />
      <game gameId="sc-1" versionId="sc-1" />
      <features tileset="jungle" minPlayers="2" maxPlayers="8" teams="4" island="false" useMapSettings="true" />
      <author authorId="auth-0" />
      <release>1998-11-20</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Typhoon</name>
        <description>
          From the tranquil jungle climate of J'larre to the unrelenting
          firestorms that rage across the plains of Char, weather patterns
          across the galaxy can vary radically. It should come as no real
          surprise that the constant, torrential downpour from the skies
          over Grissom IV appears to ignore all common laws of meteorological
          science. The chaotic ferocity of these storms has resulted in the
          severe erosion of the planet's surface, creating strange shapes in
          the terrain -- and occasionally uncovering vast amounts of resources.
          Prospectors foolish enough to tempt the tempests that thunder across
          this world must be desperate souls indeed.
        </description>
        <logo>starcraft-map-of-the-week/(5)Typhoon Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>starcraft-map-of-the-week/(5)Typhoon.jpg</preview>
      <size x="192" y="192" />
      <game gameId="sc-1" versionId="sc-1" />
      <features tileset="badlands" minPlayers="2" maxPlayers="5" island="false" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth-0" />
      <release>1998-11-25</release>
    </map>

    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Crossroads</name>
        <description>
          "All warriors shall come to a crossroads, and there shall fate pass judgement."
          -Popular Protoss proverb

          The legend of the Crossroads is one that holds great power in the minds
          of many Protoss warriors. First spoken of by Khas in the sacred scriptures,
          it is said that, "All true warriors will come to a place they do not expect
          to be and encounter those they did not expect to find. It is in that place
          the fate of the true warrior will be decided." The jungles of this remote
          planet seem to be one such site -- do not expect to enter them and depart
          unscathed.
        </description>
        <logo>starcraft-map-of-the-week/(4)Crossroads Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>starcraft-map-of-the-week/(4)Crossroads.jpg</preview>
      <size x="192" y="192" />
      <game gameId="sc-1" versionId="sc-1" />
      <features tileset="jungle" minPlayers="2" maxPlayers="4" island="false" useMapSettings="false" />
      <author authorId="auth-0" />
      <release>1998-12-04</release>
    </map>
  </maps>

  <authors>
    <author id="auth-0">
      <title>
        <name>Blizzard</name>
        <logo>authors/blizzard-logo.png</logo>
      </title>
      <url>www.blizzard.com</url>
      <email>contact@blizzard.com</email>
    </author>
    <author id="auth-2">
      <title>
        <name>Mass Media Games</name>
        <logo>authors/mass-media-logo.png</logo>
      </title>
      <url>http://massmedia.com/</url>
    </author>
  </authors>

  <games>
    <game id="sc">
      <title>
        <name>Starcraft</name>
        <logo>games/starcraft.png</logo>
      </title>
      <url>https://starcraft.com/</url>
      <versions>
        <version id="sc-0">
          <title>
            <name>Starcraft beta</name>
            <description>
              An online-only version of Starcraft open for public beta testing.
            </description>
            <logo>games/starcraft-beta.jpg</logo>
          </title>
          <downloads>
            <full name="Beta">http://www.blizzardarchive.com:80/pub/Betas/SCBeta.rar</full>
            <full name="Japanese beta">http://www.blizzardarchive.com:80/pub/Betas/SCJBeta.rar</full>
          </downloads>
          <author authorId="auth-0" />
        </version>
        <version id="sc-1">
          <title>
            <name>Starcraft</name>
            <description>
              StarCraft is set around the early 26th century. Terran exiles from
              Earth have colonized a distant area of the Milky Way galaxy called
              the Koprulu Sector, having established several governments.
              Eventually, a civil war breaks out and ends with the formation of
              the Terran Dominion.

              However, humanity soon becomes caught in a war between the Protoss
              and the Zerg, which culminates at the end of StarCraft with the death
              of the Zerg leader, the Overmind, on the Protoss homeworld of Aiur.
              Without the Overmind to command, the Zerg rampage mindlessly across
              Aiur, while the cerebrates—the secondary commanders of the
              Swarm—attempt to regain control.
            </description>
            <logo>games/starcraft.png</logo>
          </title>
          <downloads>
            <demo name="Starcraft demo">http://ftp.blizzard.com/pub/starcraft/demos/SCDemo.exe</demo>
            <patch name="PC 1.16.1">http://ftp.blizzard.com/pub/starcraft/patches/PC/SC-1161.exe</patch>
            <patch name="MAC 1.16.1">http://ftp.blizzard.com/pub/starcraft/patches/Mac/StarCraft_v1161_OSX.zip</patch>
          </downloads>
          <author authorId="auth-0" />
          <release>1998-03-31</release>
        </version>
        <version id="sc-2">
          <title>
            <name>Starcraft: Broodwar</name>
            <description>
              After the discovery of alien life in the Koprulu Sector, the
              United Earth Directorate (UED) — the international body governing
              Earth — decides to send an expeditionary force to secure the
              sector and prevent the aliens from finding Earth.
            </description>
            <logo>games/starcraft-bw.jpg</logo>
          </title>
          <downloads>
            <patch name="PC 1.16.1">http://ftp.blizzard.com/pub/broodwar/patches/PC/BW-1161.exe</patch>
            <patch name="MAC 1.16.1">http://ftp.blizzard.com/pub/broodwar/patches/Mac/Brood_War_v1161_OSX.zip</patch>
          </downloads>
          <author authorId="auth-0" />
          <release>1998-11-30</release>
        </version>
        <version id="sc-3">
          <title>
            <name>Starcraft 64</name>
            <description>
              In 2000, StarCraft 64 was released In North America for the Nintendo 64,
              co-developed by Blizzard Entertainment and Mass Media Inc. and published
              by Nintendo. The game featured all of the missions from both StarCraft
              and the expansion Brood War, as well as some exclusive missions, such as
              two different tutorials and a new secret mission, Resurrection IV.
            </description>
            <logo>games/starcraft-64.png</logo>
          </title>
          <author authorId="auth-2" />
          <release>2000-06-13</release>
        </version>
        <version id="sc-4">
          <title>
            <name>Starcraft: Remastered</name>
            <description>
              StarCraft®: Remastered upgrades the essential sci-fi strategy
              experience from beginning to end. Welcome back to the original
              game and its award-winning expansion, StarCraft: Brood War.

              We’ve remastered our units, buildings, and environments, improved
              game audio, and broadened our supported resolutions. Illustrated
              interludes bring the struggles and victories of heroes like Artanis,
              Fenix, Tassadar, Raynor and Kerrigan to life like never before.
              Most importantly, the strategy gameplay that StarCraft perfected
              years ago remains unchanged.
            </description>
            <logo>games/starcraft-remastered.png</logo>
          </title>
          <author authorId="auth-0" />
          <release>2017-07-30</release>
        </version>
      </versions>
    </game>
  </games>
</mapdb>
