<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<mapdb>
  <maps>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Beetle Island</name>
        <description>
          In a remote kingdom, the battle between the Orcs and Humans took place
          atop a huge creature. Created from the eldritch energies unleashed by
          Medivh during the birth of the Dark Portal, a giant, carnivorous beetle
          roamed the lands of Azeroth. Destroying ancient forests to satisfy its
          voracious appetite and crushing all that stood in it's path, the beetle
          became a menace to both the noble armies of the seven kingdoms and the
          savage green-skinned invaders. In an awesome display of sorcery, the likes
          of which have not been seen to this day, the great creature was polymorphed
          by the mages of the Violet Citadel just as the Orcish Death Knights
          unleashed a massive barrage of Decay spells. The result was the death
          and transformation of the beast into what is now known as Beetle Island.

          Once the greater threat was destroyed, the two armies quickly set upon
          each other again, of course...
        </description>
        <logo>warcraft2-maps-of-the-week/(6)Beetle Island Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>warcraft2-maps-of-the-week/(6)Beetle Island.jpg</preview>
      <size x="128" y="128"/>
      <game versionId="w2-bne" />
      <features tileset="Forest" minPlayers="2" maxPlayers="6" />
      <author authorId="auth-0" />
      <downloads>
        <full name="Get the creeps">warcraft2-maps-of-the-week/(6)Beetle Island.pud</full>
      </downloads>
      <release>1999-10-29</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Mountain Pass</name>
        <description>
          Towering over the fetid swamps of Draenor, the Brokenrock Mountains have
          long been a vital source of gold. The precious metal, sought after by the
          Orcish clans to fuel their rampaging war machines, has always been a prize
          worth fighting for. While an age old pact between the clans grants members
          of the Horde equal access to the vast riches of the mines, clan chieftains
          occasionally attempt to seize control of the entire mountain range for
          themselves. These greed-driven leaders learn all too soon that the
          "specialized mining techniques" of the Goblin Sappers has made the mountain
          passes very difficult to hold...
        </description>
        <logo>warcraft2-maps-of-the-week/(4)Mountain Pass Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>warcraft2-maps-of-the-week/(4)Mountain Pass.jpg</preview>
      <size x="128" y="128"/>
      <game versionId="w2-bne" />
      <features tileset="Swamp" minPlayers="2" maxPlayers="4" teams="2" />
      <author authorId="auth-0" />
      <downloads>
        <full name="Scale new heights">warcraft2-maps-of-the-week/(4)Mountain Pass.pud</full>
      </downloads>
      <release>1999-11-12</release>
    </map>
    <map>
      <title>
        <name>Cliffhanger</name>
        <description>
          The mountain ranges of Lordaeron hold many unique and mysterious treasures,
          and the valley below Griffon’s Roost is one of the more spectacular.
          Surrounded on all sides by extremely steep cliffs, the valley was
          accidentally discovered when a Dwarvish Flying Machine was blown off course
          during an unexpected storm. Expeditions have been sent overland to explore
          the valley, but the foreboding crags and horrific ice storms that sweep over
          the area have claimed the lives of many who would chart this remote place.
        </description>
        <logo>warcraft2-maps-of-the-week/(4)Cliffhanger Logo.gif</logo>
      </title>
      <preview>warcraft2-maps-of-the-week/(4)Cliffhanger.jpg</preview>
      <size x="128" y="128"/>
      <game versionId="w2-bne" />
      <features tileset="Snow" minPlayers="2" maxPlayers="4" />
      <author authorId="auth-0" />
      <downloads>
        <full name="Hang on!">warcraft2-maps-of-the-week/(4)Cliffhanger BNE.pud</full>
      </downloads>
      <release>2000-01-14</release>
    </map>
  </maps>

  <authors>
    <author id="auth-0">
      <title>
        <name>Blizzard</name>
        <logo>authors/blizzard-logo.png</logo>
      </title>
      <url>www.blizzard.com</url>
      <email>contact@blizzard.com</email>
    </author>
    <author id="auth-1">
      <title>
        <name>Cyberlore Studios</name>
        <logo>authors/cyberlore-studios.png</logo>
      </title>
      <url>http://www.cyberlore.com/</url>
    </author>
  </authors>

  <games>
    <game id="w">
      <title>
        <name>Warcraft</name>
        <logo>games/warcraft.png</logo>
      </title>
      <versions>
        <version id="w-0">
          <title>
            <name>Warcraft: Orcs and Humans</name>
            <description>
              Warcraft: Orcs &amp; Humans is the real-time fantasy strategy game
              from Blizzard Entertainment that quickly became a best seller.
              Warcraft has not only become a classic, winning many awards, but
              it has set new standards for multiplayer games. Set in the mythic
              kingdom of Azeroth, players are given the task of maintaining a
              thriving economy while building a war machine with which to destroy
              the enemy.

              By playing either the Humans or the Orcs in this saga, two separate
              story lines evolve with 12 scenarios per side telling the tale of
              the battle for Azeroth. From swords to sorcery, all the elements of
              classic fantasy are here to explore: rich forests, dark dungeons
              and bubbling swamps await the stalwart troops amassed to fight for
              dominance. Command many unique armies and creatures including
              Knights, Archers, Clerics, Warlocks, Daemons, Elementals, and the Dead.
            </description>
            <logo>games/warcraft.png</logo>
          </title>
          <author authorId="auth-0" />
          <release>1994-11-23</release>
        </version>
      </versions>
    </game>
    <game id="w2">
      <title>
        <name>Warcraft 2</name>
        <logo>games/warcraft2.png</logo>
      </title>
      <url>http://classic.battle.net/war2/</url>
      <versions>
        <version id="w2-td">
          <title>
            <name>Warcraft 2: Tides of Darkness</name>
            <description>
              With the death of the Orcish Warchief Blackhand, his underling
              Orgrim Doomhammer was quick to seize control over the most powerful
              of the Orcish forces on Azeroth. Although each day finds other
              factions growing stronger within the chaotic Horde, it seems certain
              that all of the clans will follow Orgrim's plans to hunt down and
              destroy the renegade Azerothiens wherever they choose to run...

              Sir Lothar, in charge of the scattered armies of Azeroth since
              the death of King Llane, has led his people across the Great Sea
              to the shores of Lordaeron. By enlisting the armies of Lordaeron,
              and making new allies in the Elves and Dwarves, a mighty force known
              as the Alliance has been forged. Now, the last of the once great
              armies of Azeroth seek retribution for the loss of their homeland.
            </description>
            <logo>games/warcraft2.png</logo>
          </title>
          <author authorId="auth-0" />
          <release>1995-12-09</release>
        </version>
        <version id="w2-bdp">
          <title>
            <name>Warcraft 2: Beyond the Dark Portal</name>
            <description>
              Following the destruction of Azeroth's Dark Portal by the
              victorious Alliance, the orc shaman Ner'zhul took command of the
              remaining Horde on Draenor. There, he plotted to create portals
              to other unspoiled worlds and invade each in turn. To enable the
              rituals for his dimensional conquest, Ner'zhul sent orcish forces
              through his world's intact Dark Portal in search of powerful relics
              on Azeroth. Wary of the Horde's plans, the heroes of the Alliance
              invaded Draenor to end the orcish threat forever. Facing certain
              defeat at the hands of his enemies, Ner'zhul succeeded in opening
              numerous portals to new worlds. The resulting magical stress
              shattered Draenor, trapping many of Azeroth's greatest heroes on
              Outland, the damaged remains of the planet.
            </description>
            <logo>games/warcraft2-exp.png</logo>
          </title>
          <author authorId="auth-1" />
          <release>1996-04-30</release>
        </version>
        <version id="w2-ds">
          <title>
            <name>Warcraft 2: The Dark Saga</name>
            <description>
              Warcraft II: The Dark Saga is a console version of Warcraft II: Tides of Darkness,
              with the expansion Warcraft II: Beyond the Dark Portal included. It was released
              in North America on January 6, 1997 for the Sony PlayStation and August 31, 1997
              for the Sega Saturn. It is essentially the same as Tides of Darkness and the
              expansion Beyond the Dark Portal, but it has some upgrades and slight differences.
            </description>
            <logo>games/warcraft2-ds.png</logo>
          </title>
          <author authorId="auth-0" />
          <release>1997-01-06</release>
        </version>
        <version id="w2-bne">
          <title>
            <name>Warcraft 2: Battle.net Edition</name>
            <description>
              Warcraft II: Battle.net Edition is an Battle.net-enabled version
              of Warcraft II: Tides of Darkness, with the expansion
              Warcraft II: Beyond the Dark Portal built in.

              It is essentially the same as Warcraft II, but it allows for usage
              on Battle.net. The game was also ported to be natively supported
              under Windows, unlike the original game which ran under DOS.
            </description>
            <logo>games/warcraft2-bne.png</logo>
          </title>
          <author authorId="auth-0" />
          <release>1999-09-30</release>
        </version>
      </versions>
    </game>
  </games>
</mapdb>
